[Warning]
All incidents in this drama are fictitious.
For entertainment purposes only. Please watch with caution.]
[Present]
[Naughty Babe]
[Max
Kornthas Rujeerattanavorapan]
[Nat
Natasitt Uareksit]
Tigers are powerful animals.
Elegant.
Majestic.
They are lonely hunters.
They are so lonely that sometimes I feel sorry for them.
Because if you look into their eyes,
you'll see the sadness
behind their fierce and strong look.
But I never knew
where the sadness came from.
[Director
Kittipat Champa]
If eyes are the window of our hearts,
[Joint Director
Nathavat Piyapong]
then this window is closed.
I've never been in.
[Scriptwriter
Kanyapat Jitrattanaarun(BamBam)]
I've never seen it before
what's hidden behind that window.
[Scriptwriter
crewave
Piangpaitoon Satrawaha
Preechaya Prayongsap]
I thought I was close to the true colors of Yi.
We met when I was 18.
Back then, I didn't know what it meant to be treated as part of him.
Everyone said he needed to take care of me
because I was important.
I thought it was kindness, not love.
But I couldn't help falling in love with him.
He's everything in my life.
He's the person I love the most and the person I'll spend my whole life with.
But this is my wishful thinking.
To him, this is not love.
It's not even kindness, but a duty.
Why was I like returning to the same place
in the past three years?
The harder I tried,
the further we were apart.
I'm not afraid of tigers.
But I just don't understand...
Look over here.
And I may never understand.
Please turn this way.
Look over here.
-Over here.
-Look over here.
Look over here.
Please look at the camera.
Please look over here. Please look at the camera.
Boss.
Mr. Tacha isn't in the meeting room or the bathroom.
Did you check if he was home?
Yes.
I'm sending someone to check.
But
the surveillance cameras in the house don't work.
All of them?
Yes, Boss.
What about the security guard at home?
Everyone is here today.
Mr. Phayak, I have a question.
Say it.
Mr. Phayak, when will you have good news?
I remember you've been engaged with Mr. Tacha Wongteerawit
for three years.
Right?
Or did you break up?
Is that why Tacha left just now?
What is it?
Please answer.
Please answer the questions.
I don't want to answer personal questions.
You don't answer it because it's true, right?
Do you admit it's true?
-Is it true?
-Please answer.
-Please answer the question.
Please answer.
Stop.
I'll tell you if you want to know.
But you must publish this news on every social media platform,
on the most prominent pages, for three days.
And you must abide by this condition.
I, Phayak Chatdecha Chen,
owner of Chen's Racing Circuit,
owner of Wanphayak Formula Racing Team,
Chairman of Chen's Chamber of Commerce,
and the biggest luxury car importer and distributor in Thailand,
will be getting married to Mr. Tacha Wongteerawit soon.
Once the date is set, I will hold another press conference.
Puppy.
I'm leaving.
Don't be stubborn. Don't be naughty in front of Yi.
If you can do it,
I'll come back to pick you up.
I'm sorry.
You have to cooperate with me now.
I'm really sorry, Boss.
Next time, I won't let this reporter come to the event again.
Secretary Kim has never made a mistake in media matters.
You need to improve on this matter.
Yes, Boss.
Luckily this time, I can solve the problem
and gain more media resources
without spending a penny.
Where's Diao?
Is he home?
Yes.
He's home.
But...
Don't move.
Be good.
Oh.
Okay, that's it.
Hello.
What's the matter?
Mr. Phayak's secretary asked me to check
if you're home.
I am.
Where else can I go?
Then why did you come out of the press conference alone?
I didn't feel well.
I had a stomachache.
Right, Puppy?
The CCTV cameras at home are broken. Do you know the reason?
Did you do it?
You like to play with wires, and you bit wires for fun secretly again, did you?
I seldom take you to the park.
But you want to go to the park
to have fun
and eat delicious food, right?
When I have time,
I'll take you there.
Oh, my.
What's going on?
I need to go to the bathroom.
Catch the dog for me. Now.
-Hurry.
-Okay.
Thank you.
Did he catch the dog?
Yes.
But it took a lot of time.
The puppy...
The puppy
happened to be quite aloof.
Puppy! Puppy! Don't run!
Puppy, come back here.
Oh, no.
It's good that it got away. It is ruthless.
Puppy! Puppy!
It is also a threat to me.
It has such a temperament
because Diao has always spoiled it.
Puppy! Puppy! Don't run!
Puppy!
Wait.
When the security guard went to catch the dog, where was Diao?
The security guard said Mr. Tacha went to the bathroom.
Mr. Tacha.
I've sent your dog back.
Go.
Well...
Mr. Tacha. Are you okay?
I'll get going then.
So he didn't see him?
Then why aren't the cameras at home working?
Because the dog played with wires,
the wires are broken.
Diao lied.
Well...
Why?
Diao treats the dog like his ancestor.
He can't bear for the dog to be bitten by mosquitoes.
Diao wouldn't allow this dog
to run away or bite wires.
But
the security guard said Mr. Tacha had diarrhea.
That's right.
Diao has never...
Never farted.
He doesn't fart.
He never farts in front of others. He cares about it.
Aren't you going to serve your dad?
Go down and find him.
Where is your boss?
But since you're still here, he won't go far.
Or did he abandon you?
Sorry.
The subscriber you dialed can not be reached.
What's going on?
Udon!
Diao is missing.
Find him now!
Does he realize that I'm gone?
He probably doesn't yet.
He's so busy.
He even forgot
someone was waiting for him.
It's been like this since I was 18.
Time goes fast.
But for me,
it's been a long time, Yi.
For over 6,000 nights, I had the same nightmare over and over again.
For three years, there has been a question that I've been hesitant to ask, bothering me.
I was afraid that the truth would change everything.
There is hope, yet I have to repeatedly face disappointment.
-It's tiring and discouraging.
-Thank you.
When I realized it again, those feelings had become normal.
Even though it's not normal,
and sometimes, I want to have the courage to ask you directly
whether there's something wrong.
What happened to our love?
[2023]
Yi.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
Eat up.
Why are you staring at my face?
Is there something on my face?
It's cute.
Are you kidding me?
Do you like this house?
Yes.
But you should come here often to sleep.
You've been acting strange lately
ever since Kuea and Lian's wedding,
Maybe it's because you got the bouquet.
I can't get married alone.
You need to want to get married too.
Or should we get engaged first?
Nowadays, some people get engaged in the morning and married in the evening.
What about honeymoon?
I'm a businessman. I need to know the whole situation
before I know what to do.
Yi. You're great.
Do you want a child?
You mean adopting a child?
Yes.
I didn't think that far.
Besides,
I already have Puppy.
So where are we going for our honeymoon?
Anywhere.
Where there's you.
Then here.
Is it okay now?
Switzerland. Yi.
I want to travel to Switzerland.
Why Switzerland?
I want to go to Mount Alps to see cows.
There are cows everywhere.
That's different. Yi.
Cows from Mount Alps
live in a place with fresh air.
There are beautiful grass fields and freedom.
And their horns
are very beautiful.
I thought
if I could choose what to reincarnate into in my next life,
I want to be a cow on Mount Alps.
Are you serious?
Of course.
That's why I don't eat beef.
When I was in England, I talked to my friends many times,
but I couldn't go there for a reason every time.
What are the reasons?
Why didn't I know about these before?
For the first time,
there was a snowstorm.
I put up with it.
For the second time,
Kuea had a fever.
I put up with it.
As for the third time,
I was almost there.
But my wallet was stolen.
Kuea lent me money.
But I felt sorry.
Kuea didn't go either.
That's why
I've never been there.
I didn't know
you'd been through these before.
There are a lot of things
I've been through with Kuea.
Okay.
Switzerland is fine.
I'll take you there later.
Okay.
But don't tell Kuea.
Otherwise, they two will follow us.
Okay, Yi. It's okay.
Yi.
What're you doing?
I want to try the beef from Mount Alps.
You know how much I love beef.
Don't you?
Not now. Yi.
Not now, then when?
Next life.
[2024]
Get engaged first.
Take good care of him, Yi.
We're a family now.
Congratulations.
Why don't you let them get married?
It can only end then.
Don't worry, Uncle.
Diao and I are just engaged,
but he's my life partner anyway.
I'm just waiting for the day we can get married legally.
By then,
we'll get married like other heterosexual couples.
But why doesn't your friend, the owner of Kylin Drinks,
care?
Uncle, everyone is different.
Even if we are friends,
we choose different paths in life.
Anyway,
don't abandon my son.
Dad.
Don't worry too much, Mr. Sutha.
I've always been
teaching my son to be a man
who keeps his promises.
The children of our family will follow our promises.
You can trust our morality on this.
Congratulations.
Diao.
Yi.
Thank you. Auntie.
Don't call me Auntie. Call me Mom.
You too.
Please take care of Tem and Tam.
We'll be a family soon.
Yes.
This is a gift for my new son.
But I can't drive.
Practice. Driving is not harder than Taekwondo.
Go ahead and start the engine.
Thank you.
Go help him.
When will you get married?
The law has approved it.
Is that why you called us here?
Yes.
Or do you think I'll make a will?
Unfortunately,
I'll live a long life.
I haven't said anything yet.
I know what you're thinking.
Right, Diao?
You don't have to try to win Diao over.
I didn't.
I'm with Diao.
Diao.
Tell me if he bullies you.
I'll teach him a lesson. Do you understand, kid?
Okay.
What do you think? When are you getting married?
The auspicious time the master predicted has passed.
We'll get married soon.
I've done a lot lately.
I just formed a formula team.
If you want to get married, get married quickly.
If Diao changes his mind, you'll be sad.
Okay.
Dad, let go of me. My arm will break soon.
What do you think? Are you getting married or not?
Yes, I am.
That's it.
I've solved it for you. Don't worry.
Yes, Dad. I'm not worried at all.
Let's go eat.
Do you want some? There are so many snacks.
Diao.
What's wrong? Tell me.
Did you have fun working in South Korea?
It was fun.
If you have time, try traveling.
You weren't with him.
Didn't you miss him?
I did miss him.
We've been married for over two years. I still miss him.
When we met...
Kuea.
I have a very depressed thing.
But don’t tell others if I tell you.
Not even Lian.
Okay.
Since your wedding,
he and I haven't...
Really?
Why?
Don't you like it? You don't want to do it?
Or does he have an infarction disorder?
No, that's not it.
I was shy. That's why I rejected him several times.
And since we got engaged,
he didn't come home to sleep regularly.
Where did he sleep?
In the apartment.
But I think
he has his reason.
But...
Not at all?
That's why I wanted to ask you.
Did he become like this
because he doesn't love me anymore?
Don't think too much.
No matter what, he loves you.
How could he not love you?
How about this?
If you feel depressed, you can move out.
Come to my place.
But I think
you should talk to him first
and figure out how he feels now.
I dare not.
I'm afraid of his answer.
If he says he doesn't love me anymore,
and he was with me to keep his promise to my dad,
what should I do then?
I've never had Plan B in my life.
I just wanted to marry him.
If he didn't want to get married,
it would be worse if he did.
What should I do?
You...
Your life is yours no matter what.
Yi and your dad are not the masters of your life.
You need to find a way to live a happy life on your own.
I want to be reborn as a cow in the Alps.
Don't say that. Let's finish this lifetime first.
You're a great person.
You're capable.
You're good at studying
and Taekwondo.
There must be something
that can make you happy.
I want to find my way in this world like you.
But sometimes I feel sad for my mom.
Why did she give me a name that means 'alone'?
Mom left.
Dad got remarried.
I'm just like my name, right?
I would live alone,
and feel lonely.
You still have me.
Yes.
Thank you.
I feel much better.
[There's news that Yi and a woman are in the exhibition hall.]
[Be prepared.]
[Sending the photo]
Thank you. I love this car.
Since it's yours now, drive safely.
Okay, I promise.
Don't drive fast.
Please.
Yi.
Diao.
What are you doing here?
Hello, Tacha. I...
How could you do that?
What did I do?
That's why, right?
Okay.
I see.
Yi, what happened?
I just had a nightmare.
It's just a nightmare.
It's okay, Diao.
Just a nightmare.
It's just a nightmare.
Hello. What's up, Kuea?
I'm ready to board.
You...
Calm down.
Listen to me first.
Yi had a car accident.
He was going to find you at the airport.
But the car broke down.
[An hour ago]
Look at this. Is it cute?
It's the cutest.
Lian.
Hello, Yi.
Do you know where Diao is now?
Where did you hide him?
What?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't lie to me. Diao's stuff is gone.
Where is the secret room?
I'm at Lian's house.
I've never been to the secret room. And...
If I tell you where the secret room is, it won't be a secret.
Kuea, don't mess with me.
I really don’t know.
You can ask Lian if you don't believe me.
I'm with him all day today.
You must know.
He will discuss it with you no matter what.
What are you planning?
Found him, Boss.
Mr. Narcha bought a flight to Switzerland.
He's on board now.
Switzerland?
Okay.
Yi.
Yi!
Lian.
I think Yi...
He is being taken to the hospital.
But he's still in a coma.
Why?
Why did this happen?
It's all my fault.
Yi.
Diao is here.
Diao, you can't go in.
Calm down.
With the doctors here, he will wake up.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
It's all because of me
that Yi had the accident.
You didn't do anything wrong. Don't say sorry.
But if you think you're wrong,
stay with us for now. Don't go to Switzerland.
Let's talk
after he recovers.
Don't run away now.
If you want to leave then,
but he won't let you go,
I'll take care of it.
Ensure everyone's safety.
I don't think this is an ordinary accident.
We can't let this leak out.
Yes, Sir.
Dad.
He just took medicine. He's resting.
Fortunately, the security system of this car is good,
so Yi is not badly injured.
Can I go to see him?
I'm afraid he won't see us when he wakes up.
Okay.
If he wakes up and sees you not going to Switzerland, he will be very happy.
Please take good care of him.
Yes, Dad.
Guard well.
If he wakes up, don't let him go anywhere else.
Yi.
Are you awake?
Who are you?
Yi.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Who are you?
Yi, I'm Diao.
Well...
You're the only one here. There's no one else.
I'm Tacha Wongteerawit.
Tacha is just a seven-year-old kid.
Don't tease me.
I'm not joking.
Does it hurt?
Go get my dad and the others.
You can leave now.
You don't remember me?
Or
have you lost your memory?
Get out.
How can you talk to your friend politely when you lose your memory?
Are we close?
You don't even remember me?
-Can't you remember?
-You're so annoying.
Stop joking.
This is Diao,
your fiancee. Why can't you remember him?
I feel so sorry for Yi.
He can't even remember me.
I don't know if he can recover his memory.
-Mr. Gun.
-Young Master Diao is missing.
Mr. Tacha bought a ticket to Switzerland.
Diao.