Warning: All occurrences happened
in this series are fictional
and for an entertainment purpose only.
Viewer discretion required.
[Yi Phayak Chatdecha Chen]
[By Kornthas Rujeerattanavorapan]
[Kon Diao Tacha Wongteerawit]
[By Nat Natasitt Uareksit]
[Kuea Keerati]
[Lian Kilen Wang]
[By Chawarin Perdpiriyawong
By Pruk Panich]
[Silsamue by Pharinyakorn Khansawa
Nuea by Koraphat Lamnoi]
[Secretary Aon by Supha Sangaworawong]
[Makorn by Penpetch Benyakul]
[Sattha by Teerapong Leowrakwong]
[Sathaporn by Tawatson Plengsiriwat]
[Stepmother Orn by Thanyaporn Sontikan]
Let me check your lungs.
Excuse me.
Take a deep breath.
Let me see your eyes as well.
Look straight, please.
According to your vital signs,
your physical condition is normal.
You only sprained your arm.
According to the x-ray results,
there are no fractures.
I'll keep your arm bandaged
to minimize your movement.
I'm Phayak, The Indestructible.
Try not to move your arm.
You must be under
the supervision of your relatives.
You'll feel better in 2-3 weeks.
Avoid lifting heavy objects
or crushing your arm.
Can you tell me your name again, please?
My name?
I'm Phayak Chatdecha Chen.
Chatdecha is my middle name after my mom's.
Her name is Chatchai.
My surname, Chen,
is derived from my father's ancestor.
He's the one pouting over there.
What about the person next to your father?
Do you recall him?
He told me his name was Kon Diao, Tacha.
I don't think that's his name.
Tacha, whom I know, is just seven years old.
How old are you?
What about you?
Yi!
I'm sorry for that, doctor.
You're already 32 years old.
This is Kon Diao, your fiancé.
Why don't you remember him?
What fiancé? Don't joke with me.
Do you remember what you were doing
or where you were going
before the accident?
What is your most recent memory?
I can't recall.
I remember my dad.
I remember my mom.
But I don't remember what happened.
According to the diagnosis findings,
your physical condition is normal.
Because you passed out
and woke up with no memory of the incident,
as well as recalling this person
as a 7-year-old child,
I'd like to refer your case to neurosurgeons
and emergency diagnostic radiologists.
I'd also like to draw your blood
to further investigate the cause.
Okay.
Hia.
Have some water.
I've had enough.
Drinking a lot of water makes me want to pee.
Then, tell me if you want anything.
I want to sleep.
I'm sleepy.
Okay.
You don't have to watch over me.
I won't leave you.
My father's guards are everywhere.
In case you have something to do.
It's fine.
I can stay here.
What do I usually call you?
Honey,
darling,
my love, or Nong?
It's Nong.
You usually call me Nong Diao.
You call yourself Hia.
Really?
Are we actually engaged
or am I being tricked by my dad?
We're actually engaged.
How is that possible?
We're both male.
The same-sex marriage law
has now been approved, Hia.
It's 2026.
Same-sex couples can now lawfully marry.
Do we love each other?
I mean, when did we get engaged?
We've been engaged for about 3 years.
3 years? Why didn't we get married?
It's because... Actually, we were breaking up.
Even if we've been engaged for 3 years?
Why is that?
You cheated on me.
That's not true.
It's impossible.
Despite my memory loss,
I will never forget what Dad taught me.
He told me to love Kon Diao.
I mean, he told me to be loyal and faithful.
I would never forget that.
You didn't forget.
You were stubborn.
- You wouldn't follow your dad's advice.
- I was stubborn?
- Yes, you were.
- That's not true.
I don't recall any of those.
Yes, you don't.
That's why you have to believe me.
You ended our relationship and cheated on me.
I was going to move to Europe for a while.
Why are you still here?
Did I let you down?
Are you mad at me?
You probably are,
because I don't remember anything.
If I have ever failed you,
I'm sorry.
It's fine if you hate me.
I really don't understand why I did that.
And the fact that I mistook you
for a seven-year-old boy...
I must have lost my mind.
I'm no longer 7 years old.
I'm 25 now.
You're still the same.
Did you say you wanted to sleep?
I'll let you sleep.
I'll find something to eat.
Kon Diao.
How's Yi doing?
He's better now.
But...
he lost his memory.
Really? How?
You should see it for yourself.
I don't know how to explain it.
You can see him first.
I'll have a talk with Kon Diao for a second.
Are you okay?
Let's talk over there.
Is he really that bad?
Why is it so terrifying?
You should've seen his eyes
when he looked at me.
He was blanking.
He looked at me
as if I were someone he didn't know.
Don't overthink it.
He'll be fine.
What if he won't?
What if he forgets me forever?
Don't cross the bridge until you come to it.
You have to stay strong.
There's one thing that I find strange.
If I tell you this, can you not tell anyone?
Sure.
You can tell me everything.
Don't tell Hia Lian either.
Mm.
Hia Yi said that Kon Diao Tacha,
whom he is acquainted with,
- is a 7-year-old boy.
- What?
7 years old?
I don't know how he met me when I was seven.
I don't recall ever seeing him before.
It's true that my family is indebted to Makorn,
but the first time I saw him
after returning from the UK
was when I was eighteen.
You two may have met when you were younger,
and he recalls you.
He's 7 years older than us.
It's not strange.
Why would you want me to keep it a secret?
Why don't you just ask Hia Yi or your family?
I don't know. I think it's strange.
It's as if I've never heard of it before.
Perhaps this will explain a lot about
my relationship with him.
It might be the reason we have to marry.
It might be nothing.
Nurse answering.
Yes, I'll get to it.
Zen, get the medication for room 10.
Back off.
Let go of me! Let me go!
- Yi!
- Let me go!
Take it easy, Yi.
- Let go of me!
- Yi.
- Yi!
- Let go of me! Let me go!
Let go of me!
- Stay still.
- Let go of me!
Let me go!
Thank you.
Hia,
I'm sorry.
It's my fault that...
you've been in this situation.
Lele! Where are you, Lele?
Lele!
Kon Diao! Kon Diao!
Kon Diao! Uncle!
Uncle!
Can someone help us?
Help! Lele has escaped!
Can somebody help us? Now!
Hey! Help us!
I, Phayak Chatdecha Chen,
the owner of Chen Circuit,
will marry Mr. Tacha Wongteerawit shortly.
Aon, Kon Diao is missing!
Kuea Keerati Wang, where did you hide him?
Where's your secret house, Kuea?
I found him, sir.
He's booked a flight to Switzerland.
The flight leaves at 10.30 P.M.
Kon Diao.
Let me go.
Let me go. Let me go.
I told you to let me go.
If you two don't let me go
and I escape,
I'll absolutely end you.
Let me go, now!
Are you okay, Mr. Phayak?
Where's my phone? I need it.
Your phone is with Aon, your secretary.
I know who he is.
Go get him.
Now!
Yes, sir?
Where's Kon Diao?
How far has he gotten?
Mr. Tacha just left at 10 P.M.
He said he'd stay with Nong at home.
He'll come here again in the morning.
Didn't he go to Switzerland?
Mr. Tacha didn't go anywhere, sir.
He's been here, taking care of you,
since the beginning.
He just left a few hours ago.
You've already met him, sir.
When?
Since the morning.
You woke up and saw Mr. Tacha, sir.
Why can't I recall anything?
Well...
You lost your memory, sir.
Do you remember what you were doing
or where you were going
before the accident?
- What is your most recent memory?
- I can't recall.
I remember my dad.
We were breaking up.
- You cheated on me.
- It's impossible.
I will never forget what Dad taught me.
He told me to love Kon Diao.
Did I really lose my memory?
What happened?
You've...
done so many things.
What have I done?
Try thinking about it.
I'll let you sleep.
I'll find something to eat.
Wait. Don't enter just yet.
How are you doing?
I told you to wait, sir.
You're talking to your friend so politely
after you've lost your memory, huh?
Who are you?
You don't even remember me?
I'm offended.
Are we close?
We're really close.
We have a profound bond, to put it honestly.
Are you telling me that you and I are...
having an affair?
No, that's not true.
Where's Kon Diao?
Do you remember him?
No.
Aside from my dad, he's the only person I know.
He's with Nu Kuea outside.
Nu Kuea?
Who's Nu Kuea?
My love.
- Your love?
- Right.
We've been married for over 3 years.
Nu Kuea is Kon Diao's best friend.
And you're my best friend.
I'm Lian.
I own the Kilen brand of water,
which you drink.
Water?
Kilen?
Lian?
You're starting to remember?
Take it easy, Yi. You'll remember it.
We were breaking up.
- You don't even remember me?
- We've been engaged for about 3 years.
- You cheated on me.
- Why don't you remember your fiancé?
Urgh!
- I can't think of anything.
- Calm down, Yi.
Take it easy.
What the f*ck is wrong with me?
I can't think of anything.
Where are you going?
Sit right here.
Lian.
I kicked him.
Though I can't recall it,
I will never forget that.
Mr. Lian might never forget it either, sir.
Great, he deserved it.
What happened after that?
I can't recall anything.
- Yi!
- Hey! It hurts!
Guards!
Back off.
Anyone who blocks me will be fired.
Mr. Makorn has given us the order
- not to let you go anywhere.
- Forget him.
How could you cage me here?
He's not a cop.
The patient is on a rampage.
Please have a nurse come in.
Hey! Let me go.
Let me go. Urgh.
- Yi.
- Let me go.
- Let go of me.
- Yi, calm down.
- Let me go.
- Stay still.
- Let go of me.
- Yi.
Take it easy, Yi.
- Let me go.
- Yi.
- Let go of me.
Let me go.
- Stay still.
- Let go of me.
Come inside, Aon, and we'll discuss.
Tell them to wait outside.
Wait outside.
Aon,
my memory has now returned.
I'm still confused about
what happened yesterday.
You must not tell anyone
about my current condition.
Don't tell my dad either.
Don't ever tell Kon Diao.
Yes, sir.
Don't tell the guards.
Replace them with our people tomorrow.
I don't want my dad's people messing around.
Yes, sir.
I have something for you to do.
Lian...
Hello, Mr. Lian. I've arrived at your house.
Please.
What is it?
Yi's gone into a coma.
Yi.
I'll find Nu Kuea.
It's too late.
You have to go to the hospital now, sir.
Let me call Nu Kuea first.
You have to go now.
Please.
Yi!
What kind of joke are you making?
Are you so concerned about me
that you came here in your pajamas?
What's your problem?
I want your help.
Before asking for my help,
won't you say sorry to me first?
Sit right here.
Sorry for what?
Did I just get kicked for nothing?
You also tricked me to get here.
You're talking too much.
Yi, look what you've done.
Be careful.
I'll have Kon Diao move in with me and Nu Kuea.
- And because you lost your memory...
- Lian!
Your memory has now returned, hasn't it?
Instead of having Nu Kuea
and Kon Diao with you,
why don't you let Nu Kuea live with me
and Kon Diao?
We'll see if Nu Kuea will stay with you
or Kon Diao.
Well, it depends.
You're not the same person you used to be.
Yi, who you can't recall, is
kind, sweet, polite,
and very friendly.
Me? Friendly?
Look at you now.
How can you be certain
that he's going to be with you?
Fine.
I'm sorry.
Aon!
Is there something wrong?
Fine, I'm sorry.
For what?
For kicking you.
I only accept apologies in cryptocurrency.
What?
Do I have to give you my coins?
Your memory returned,
but you lied to me.
- How would you know?
- Why wouldn't I?
Done.
Apology accepted.
What's your problem?
Why did you trick me to get here?
Kon Diao told me that we were breaking up
because I cheated on him.
Why did he say that?
I also want to know.
From your love, maybe.
Don't mention my love.
I'll find out soon.
But I'm wondering...
why he lied to me.
Why did he say I cheated on him?
Is there something more to it?
Why did you bring me here?
I have no idea about this at all.
Why don't you talk to Kon Diao?
He wouldn't tell me the truth.
He was leaving me for Switzerland.
Though he seems obedient,
he's actually stubborn.
He would never tell me the truth.
If my memory didn't return,
I would have to let him go.
What are you going to do?
I'll pretend.
I'll pretend I lost my memory.
Now, we'll see what that naughty boy will do.
I know some excellent acting coaches.
Do you want me to contact them for you?
You're the one who has to learn how to pretend.
It's not funny.
You'll also have to pretend.
And you'll do it perfectly.
If you believe it,
Nu Kuea will also believe it.
No, I don't want to lie to my love.
I'm not saying you have to lie.
Just pretend that my memory hasn't returned.
Please.
I have to win Kon Diao over.
There are no winners or losers.
You don't know what he's thinking.
He doesn't know what you're thinking.
If you want to understand each other,
you have to be his doggo.
Look how he treats Nong.
Yeah.
Our lives are always changing.
If you want to start over with him, just do it.
If you want to pretend that
you've lost your memory
and are crazy,
I'll help you.
Thank you for your understanding.
Okay.
If people understand that
my memory hasn't returned,
I might be able to see things more clearly.
It's not only about Kon Diao.
The incident has tarnished
Chen's Dealer's reputation.
I checked all my cars.
Especially since I was driving it by myself,
this shouldn't have happened.
I wouldn't lose control at that speed.
Someone must have messed with my car.
Are you sure?
I can't say I'm sure,
but I believe this accident was
caused by someone.
I have to find out who they are.
Nong...
I really feel sorry for Hia, Nong.
He's not only injured
but also suffers from memory loss.
He doesn't even remember me.
I'm not sure if he'll remember me someday.
It might be good for him, though.
He won't feel anything
when I'm gone.
I won't have to worry about him.
You too, Nong.
If I'm gone,
you'll have to learn to forget me.
If I couldn't come back to take you with me,
you'd have to learn to be alone.
You are better than me.
Do you know why you ended up like this?
You mean in the hospital?
I mean, how do you end up trying to figure out
why he's leaving you?
He's not leaving me.
He just wants space.
Did he say he wanted space?
Why would you rub it in?
Yi,
before you can address an issue,
you must first identify its root cause.
I don't know what he's thinking.
Of course.
If you knew, you wouldn't be like this.
Try asking yourself
why you were so cold to him.
Why are you engaged but not married?
Something happened in the past that I...
He almost died because of me.
I also ruined someone's life.
Can I take Lele for a walk?
I don't think you should, Mr. Yi.
Lele's not in a good mood.
That's because he wants to go for a walk.
- I think...
- Don't be scared of my dad.
Don't follow me.
I'll handle him.
Okay.
Lele! Where are you, Lele?
Lele!
Come here, Lele!
Where are you, Lele?
Lele!
Come here, Lele! Hurry!
Where are you hiding, Lele?
Where are you, Lele?
Come here, Lele!
Come to me.
Lele!
Kon Diao!
Uncle!
Can someone help us?
Can somebody help us?
Help us!
Lele has escaped! Can somebody help us?
Now! Help!
Hey! Help us!
Help us! Help!
Now!
Come here! Hey!
Kon Diao recently lost his mother.
He has few memories of his mother.
And this happened...
I'll take care of everything.
You can trust me.
Following what happened that day,
Lele was transferred
to a wildlife rescue center.
Although it is legal
for my family to keep Lele,
Dad believed we should no longer do so.
Lele's caretaker turned blind in both eyes.
He went from being a diligent worker
to becoming disabled.
His family left him.
Not long after that, he left this world.
And Kon Diao...
He was no different than a doll.
He became a boy with breath but no soul.
I was the reason
he lost most of his childhood memories.
It was completely my fault.
At the time, I never even...
apologized.
That's why I've been
repeating the same nightmare.
It made me scared of approaching him
in case I made another mistake.
The stronger our relationship became,
the more nightmares I had.
Each morning after I wake up,
I feel guilty.
I still don't trust myself
to be the person
who can actually make him happy.
Have you ever told Kon Diao about this?
Not just Kon Diao.
I've never told anyone about this.
This is the first time.
You should tell him directly.
I think he's mature now.
He might understand you.
He might understand,
but will he really forgive me?
He almost died because of me.
He lost his memory.
And my dad sent him to study in the UK.
He was practically cut off from his own family.
You told me it was a good thing.
I don't know if it's best for Kon Diao.
Is this why you keep putting off...
the wedding?
It's not the only reason.
After Lele's incident,
the Wongteerawit family
won't stop demanding more.
His father is not the major concern.
It's Sathaporn, Kon Diao's stepmother.
She acts like a wire-puller,
always manipulating Kon Diao's father
to take advantage of the Chen family.
I think they're holding Kon Diao captive
in order to force my dad to do things for them.
On the day we were engaged,
Dad had the Wongteerawit family
sign an engagement contract
with the condition that if we did not marry,
cheated on each other,
or broke up within 5 years,
if the Chen family broke the contract,
we'd have to pay the Wongteerawit
family money for the racing track,
but if the Wongteerawit family was at fault,
the land would belong to the Chen family.
I'm not okay with the conditions.
I'm still trying to figure out
how to cope with it.
Does the Wongteerawit family
own the racing circuit's land?
Just part of it, not all.
They made my dad buy the land.
My dad then bought the land around it
and built the racing track on it.
This is a serious matter.
There's something more serious.
I just realized.
The car that was involved
in the accident was Kon Diao's.
This is a gift for my new son.
Does this mean...
Right, someone must have messed with the car.
I was not the target.
It was Kon Diao.
Who do you suspect?
Who else is there besides the Wongteerawits?
He never had any disputes with anyone.
I have to be pessimistic.
I will find out the truth.
They tried to wake a sleeping tiger.
Unfortunately, I was the driver.
I was able to control the car, so I survived.
Therefore, Lian,
you have to help me.
You must convince everyone
that I still have amnesia.
I will.
We'll take care of him after this.
Where's Hia Yi?
He's undergoing an MRI scan, sir.
He'll be back soon.
Thank you.
Alright.
According to your blood vessels
and brain tissue,
no abnormalities were found.
But why can't I recall anything, doctor?
Ouch!
My head is in a lot of pain.
Is it?
Your memory loss has nothing to do
with your headache, though.
I didn't get much sleep last night.
Hmm... It's probably caused by stress.
Then, I'll write a report
for the doctor in charge of your case
to provide you with painkillers.
Doctor, will my memory return?
Hm...
I don't have an answer yet.
I'll write a report
for the doctor in charge of your case
to further examine.
You might be suffering from
acute amnesia of unknown cause.
So... I have acute amnesia, right?
- That's right.
- Okay.
Great.
Kon Diao.
Do you want me to wake Mr. Tacha...
Hia, why did you kiss me?
What were you trying to do?
Kissing you, obviously.
Kissing me...?
You said you would break up with me
after being discharged from the hospital, Hia.
When did I promise you that we would break up?
Where's your evidence?
Do you have any documents?
Hia has become a different person
since having amnesia.
He's even warmer than a microwave.
You seem fine.
What did you do to make Diao frustrated?
I don't know. I lost my memory.
You can't trick me.
You don't have to believe that I have amnesia.
I will make use of my amnesia
to uncover the truth.
That bulging-eyed dog, be careful,
or I'll turn you into meatballs.
Why would you scare her like that?
Even if you lost your memory...
Or...