Warning: All occurrences happened
in this series are fictional
and for an entertainment purpose only.
Viewer discretion required.
You're talking to your friend so politely
after you've lost your memory, huh?
Are we close?
You don't even remember me?
I can't think of anything.
Don't kid me.
This is Kon Diao, your fiancé.
Why don't you remember him?
I really feel sorry for Hia, Nong.
He doesn't even remember me.
I'm not sure if he'll remember me someday.
Aon, Kon Diao is missing!
He's booked a flight to Switzerland.
Kon Diao!
[Yi Phayak Chatdecha Chen]
[By Kornthas Rujeerattanavorapan]
[Kon Diao Tacha Wongteerawit]
[By Nat Natasitt Uareksit]
[Kuea Keerati]
[Lian Kilen Wang]
[By Chawarin Perdpiriyawong
By Pruk Panich]
[Silsamue by Pharinyakorn Khansawa
Nuea by Koraphat Lamnoi]
[Secretary Aon by Supha Sangaworawong]
[Makorn by Penpetch Benyakul]
[Sattha by Teerapong Leowrakwong]
[Sathaporn by Tawatson Plengsiriwat]
[Stepmother Orn by Thanyaporn Sontikan]
Hia...
I'm sorry, Hia.
Are you okay?
And... What were you...
What were you doing?
Kissing you, obviously.
Why did you kiss me?
I don't know. I just wanted to.
Nothing more.
You were cute,
so I wanted to kiss you.
We usually kiss, don't we?
We're fiancés.
No, we don't.
We've kissed, haven't we?
I don't think we've never kissed, though.
You should've asked me nicely.
Do I have to?
You do.
Then... may I?
No, you may not.
I want a kiss!
I want a kiss. A kiss! Kiss me.
Hia...
No whining, please.
If you won't let me kiss you,
you have to kiss away my pain.
I was hurt because of you.
Fine.
May your pain go away!
Get well soon, Hia.
We're here.
Nong!
This is Nong, my dog.
You gave her to me.
Do you remember that?
You two were madly in love with each other.
You were best friends.
You shared your bed and food.
You spent every night together.
I don't think that's right.
Nong, why are you facing that way?
Are you mad at Hia?
There, there.
It's okay.
He doesn't remember you
because he has lost his memory.
Hia, she's still mad.
Can you make up with her?
With her? I don't know how to do that.
Just give her a kiss,
and she'll stop being mad.
Babe, I think you've gone too far.
Fine!
Here.
Hia!
Let's go, Nong.
Are you still mad at me?
I told you to kiss Nong,
not me.
Oh, yeah? I didn't know.
I thought you meant Nong Diao.
Are you going back to your condo right away?
What condo?
Usually, when you dropped me off,
you'd stay here for just a moment
and return to your condo.
I won't leave you. I'll stay here.
- Usually...
- Well, this is not usual.
Who will look after me if I return to my condo?
But we broke up, Hia.
Besides,
you haven't stayed here in a long time.
I can't recall.
We talked about this the other day.
You said you would break up with me
after being discharged from the hospital, Hia.
It's because I was confused.
But you promised me.
Where's your evidence?
Do you have any documents?
When did I promise you that we would break up?
Before you lost your memory.
You told me you wanted to break up,
and you would marry someone else.
Do you think you can fool me, Nong Diao?
Who?
Why would I know how many mistresses you had?
Just find one of them,
and then we'll talk about this.
You cheated on me.
You want me to go and search
for your mistresses?
You're such an irresponsible person.
You remember it, but I don't.
Go find them, since you can recall.
If you can't recall, just believe me.
He suddenly started smart-mouthing.
Should I give him one more kiss on the lips?
If you don't have proof,
I won't accept that
we made an agreement.
I don't remember anything.
What about you? You're caught in 4K.
- Why are you making excuses?
- What do you mean?
Your engagement ring.
Though I've lost my memory,
I'll never forget Chen's ancestral diamond ring
on your left ring finger.
It hurts. Let go of me!
You wouldn't wear it if we'd already broken up.
You told me it was just a small diamond,
- and you could just buy a new one.
- Liar!
I would never say that.
This diamond ring was...
given to the Chen family's ancestor
by the Qing Dynasty emperors.
It's an heirloom that's been passed down
for hundreds of years.
It has a story behind it.
I'm not that kind to give it away to my ex!
Fine! Take it back then.
Try taking it off.
I'll beat you to death.
If you beat me,
- I'll also beat you.
- Kon Diao!
You must understand that
if you beat someone,
they may beat you back.
You're not the greatest person in the world!
I tried to hold it back many times,
but you were just a stubborn person!
You were always upset.
- You're a bad guy.
- Tacha Wongteerawit!
Now you remember me,
Mr. Phayak Chatdecha Chen?
Alright! Come on!
Anything more? Say it!
Ouch!
- Ouch!
- Hia!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
You teased me.
You're not worried about me anymore?
I am.
Don't be so stubborn, Hia.
Okay.
I won't be stubborn.
I'll do anything you want.
But may I please stay with you?
Fine.
- But you have to promise me...
- No!
No more promises.
I don't want to have another argument with you.
I'm tired.
You're too stubborn.
I'm not stubborn.
You're the one who's stubborn.
I'm tired.
My arm hurts.
May I please recharge?
Recharge...?
- May I have a kiss?
- Hia...
Please.
Please have some mercy on this sick guy.
This is your bedroom.
You can sleep here.
I'll sleep in the small bedroom.
- Share the bed with me.
- No.
Why not?
What's the problem?
- Well... we broke up.
- Don't use that as an excuse.
Don't be selfish, Hia.
- Hia...
- I told you to share the bed with me,
and you should.
Hia, let me go!
I need someone to take care of me.
Hia, but...
No buts.
We've done this before, right?
No.
Hia...
I just realized.
When you lie, you'll shake
and avoid eye contact with me.
You're wrong. That's nonsense.
You like it too, don't you?
What do you mean by "it"?
"It" means... "this."
Ouch! Ouch!
I'm sorry.
Kon Diao, calm down.
Take it easy, Kon Diao.
Get yourself together, Tacha.
May I please come in?
Nong, are you hungry?
Why are you barking?
You must be hungry.
Let's go eat.
That bulging-eyed dog...
Do you want some more?
I'll give you some more.
You're eating happily
after ruining our moment, huh?
I could just eat you up.
You're too cute. Why are you so cute?
I want to squeeze you.
Let me give you a squeeze.
Nong, you're safe now.
I'm here for you.
Mr. Phayak is now recuperating at his home.
As for the accident, it's still not over.
The car is still in police custody.
Right. My special team has already issued
a statement regarding Mr. Yi's accident
and distributed it to various media outlets.
Great.
Please ensure that any media does not mislead
or tarnish the Chen family's business image.
We, my special team and I,
will ensure that they...
zip it.
Thank you for assisting us
during this difficult time, Secretary Kim,
despite the fact that
you just gave birth to your child.
I'm willing to do everything,
literally everything,
for Mr. Yi and the Chen family.
Please excuse me.
I'm going to breastfeed my baby.
I have a family now.
Please excuse me.
Increase our security posture at all times
until Mr. Phayak issues an updated order.
- Yes.
I'm hungry. What's the food?
I ordered a pork blood soup
from your favorite restaurant.
You should eat up.
Konn Diao, where are you going?
Come and eat with me.
I ordered only one serving.
Order more of it, then.
I'd rather not.
I'm not a fan of offal.
If you don't eat it, neither will I.
You can't do that.
You must eat and take your medicine.
You haven't eaten anything today.
Ouch!
Ouch! My arm hurts!
Where does it hurt?
I think it's been swollen
since I fell off the bed.
Whoa! It's really swollen.
Should you go back to the hospital?
I'll take you there.
I'll feel better
when I take the medications.
Can you please feed me?
Why are you begging like a child?
Am I cute?
You should hurry back to the hospital.
I think you need to
get your brain checked again.
Are you saying that
you like the other version of me better?
I don't like any version of you.
Okay.
I want you to go back to your old self quickly.
So, I'll feed you.
However, you have to finish your food,
take your medicine, and rest.
Stop doing something crazy!
Okay!
As long as you don't leave me,
I'll do anything you tell me to.
Then, sit on the floor.
Just kidding. You can sit on the chair.
You'll get tired.
I'm going to feed you now.
You like pork blood curd, right?
Ah!
You really like it, don't you?
I want some liver pieces.
Do you like dog meat?
Nong would be okay.
I won't let you!
Give me a piece of liver.
You can't live alone anymore, can you?
This is just the first day.
I'll teach you a lesson.
You're worn out now, huh?
Have a good night, Hia.
Thank you.
Mr. Phayak is at his home now.
There's one thing
I'm not sure if I should tell you.
One or two more would be great,
don't you think?
It's nothing much.
It's just that...
Mr. Phayak's lost his memory.
Nong, keep it down!
Noisy!
Jeez!
Wait. Wait.
Mr. Aon, how did you get in here?
What are you doing here?
Hello, Mr. Tacha.
I couldn't reach Mr. Phayak.
May I know how he's doing?
He's asleep. He hasn't woken up yet.
Where are you going?
Mr. Makorn would like to speak with him
at the mansion in two hours.
I see...
I'll wake him up for you.
Please take a seat and wait here.
Okay, there's still time.
- 2 hours.
- Yes.
2 hours?
Okay.
Let's go, Nong. Let's wake Hia up.
What should we do, Nong?
He seems to be sleeping soundly.
I don't want to bother him.
Wait. Wait.
That bulging-eyed dog!
Be careful,
or I'll turn you into meatballs.
Hia...
Even if you've lost your memory,
you still want to eat Nong?
What I've been thinking is coming true?
No.
I...
Why would you scare her like that?
Even if you lost your memory...
Or...
Do you really like dog meat?
Mr. Aon, your secretary, is here
to take you to the mansion to see Makorn.
That bulging-eyed dog, you almost ended me.
I must be more careful.
Diao!
Can you help me get dressed?
It's hard to do it with one hand.
I can help you, sir.
You don't have to.
Let Kon Diao do it.
Hia!
Hia!!
Thank you.
You've been engaged for 3 years now.
Why are you still shy, Kon Diao?
He's the same person.
Why would your heart tremble?
Don't forget what your intention is.
Don't forget what you intend to do.
I completed all of the company work
as you asked, sir.
As for the news of your accident,
everything is under our control.
Don't let anyone know about my symptoms.
Also, check to see
if anyone is acting suspiciously.
Yes, sir.
Where's the car?
At the factory, sir.
We just got it back from the police last night.
Send the best possible mechanic team
to figure out the cause.
I've already sent one, sir.
I think we'll find out soon.
Why does Dad want to see me?
Did he tell you?
No, sir.
I asked, but...
he said it was a family matter.
A family matter?
How's Kon Diao?
It's me, your son, who got into an accident.
It's not Kon Diao.
You seem fine.
Do you want me to call Kon Diao here, then?
I want to talk to you.
I know what happened.
I don't think you know everything.
Right. Not everything.
I just want to know why.
What did you do to make Diao frustrated?
I don't know. I lost my memory.
Don't ever lie to me.
I'm not lying.
I really have amnesia.
You were there
when the doctor told me I'd lost my memory.
I've been raising you since you were a baby.
I can see through you.
You can't trick me.
You don't have to believe that I have amnesia,
but please believe in my strategies.
I will make use of my amnesia
to uncover the truth.
So you have no idea
what you did to upset him so badly
that he would leave you?
- He didn't leave me.
- He almost did.
You're an idiot.
You didn't take good care of him.
You were obsessed with your work.
Who would have that much patience?
Are you talking about me or you, Dad?
I've made mistakes.
That's why I'm educating you now.
You don't have to look up to me
as a role model for stuff like this.
The river has no return.
I can't go back in time and undo what happened.
However, you have a chance to start over.
Make up with him.
Between me and Kon Diao,
- you prefer...
- Kon Diao.
I'm your son.
- I am your son.
- Kon Diao.
Fine.
Appreciate that.
How's it going? Spill the tea.
I'm not very sure now, Kuea.
- Is it because you're worried about Hia Yi?
- Mm...
Hia has become a different person
since having amnesia.
How?
He's now...
Now what?
He's now so sweet!
- What? Hia Yi?
- Yeah.
It's unbelievable, right?
He's turned into a needy person.
He's even warmer than a microwave.
Wait. I think it's safe to say
he's as warm as a BBQ grill.
Wow!
When I'm near him, my heart melts.
Whoa!
You have now become a pork belly!
He's too sweet to handle, Kuea.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's eat.
Come on. Let's eat.
You're so good at ruining my moment.
Get up. Let's eat.
Why are you so hungry?
Talking to you made me hungry.
But there's one thing that confuses me.
- What is it?
- Well, Hia...
I think he hates Nong's guts.
Even if he has amnesia, he still hates her.
You know what I'm thinking?
It made me think that
if the old him didn't want to marry me
and his memory returned,
he'd be the same as before.
I do want him to recover,
but that might also mean that
I have to leave him.
Try thinking about it the other way around.
The fact that he is as warm
as a BBQ grill right now
might be due to his deep love for you.
Don't cross the bridge until you come to it.
Now, I think you should put
your own needs first.
You should talk things out with Hia as well.
About moving to Switzerland,
if you still want to go there,
I think you should go.
Meanwhile, take advantage of this time
to reconsider your feelings.
Will I be able to do that?
Of course.
Whatever you decide,
I'll always be here for you.
I love you, Kuea.
I love you too.
Hia Yi!
Hia...
How did you get here?
Aon took me here.
The door's not locked.
Who the hell are you?
Who's this, Kon Diao?
It's Kuea, Hia.
I'm Kuea Keerati Wang,
the life partner of Lian Kilen Wang,
your best friend.
He also owns this house.
I see. You're his husband.
How dare you pinch Kon Diao's cheeks?
Why can't I?
We've been like this for a long time.
Kon Diao, are you cheating on me?
I'm not, Hia.
We're just friends.
Well...
We really do love each other so much.
Like, very much.
I've not just pinched his cheeks.
I've also kissed him on the cheek.
- Have you?
- That's enough, Kuea.
I've done things you've never done.
What have you done with Diao?
- What?
- Taking a roller-coaster ride, maybe?
Jeez! Stop it. That's enough.
You and Hia Lian also do stuff like this,
don't you?
Stuff like this?
I love you, Yi.
I love you too, Lian.
- You're the cutest.
- You're so cute.
We've never done that!
We're just friends, though.
He's not cheating on you.
- He's not like you, Hia Yi.
- What the hell are you talking about, kiddo?
Before the accident occurred
and before we broke up,
- you really did cheat on me.
- That's not true.
- I've never cheated on you.
- You have.
You just lost your memory.
That's impossible.
I would never do that.
You're so convinced, huh?
But someone who doesn't know how to lie
told me about this.
He would never lie to me.
Who? When?
Say it!
- Hi, Tacha.
- How can you do that to me?
Ing-ing Chatchada.
She's a celebrity
who bought a car from your showroom.
The other one is Aun-aun, a flight attendant.
Hey, Kon Diao.
You might think I know nothing.
In fact, it's the opposite.
You know everything? How?
You probably don't know what you've done,
but I do remember everything.
Here.
Isn't that the Princess Gang?
What is the Princess Gang?
There. She's Ing-ing Chatchada.
You said she was your distant relative.
Right. It's her.
Should we say hi to her?
I don't think we should.
We haven't spoken since we were kids.
Wait. Hia Yi's here.
Ladies,
can you give me some time to talk to Hia?
Then, we'll go to the toilet.
Hia! That's too much!
You think he's cheating on Kon Diao?
Of course.
I don't think he is. Believe me.
Stop it.
- But...
- This is none of your business.
Don't take sides.
We'll handle this.
If we're here,
how will we know what they're talking about?
The Buddha taught us
not to believe everything right away.
You should first employ your mindfulness,
intelligence,
and dedicated thought and consideration.
Fine.
If this was his first time,
I wouldn't believe it.
But something similar happened before.
You sent me the photos, Sil.
Nuea,
can you buy me a bottle of water?
Nuea, I have to go now.
That's Yi, Kon Diao's fiancé.
That woman...
No, no, Sil. Don't think this way.
It can't be what I'm thinking.
No, Sil!
Kon Diao is Kuea's friend.
Kuea's my friend.
It can't be.
No, Sil!
I have to help my friend.
Sil, you can't take photos of them.
You don't have their permission. It's a sin.
It's a sin.
It's not, Sil.
It is.
It's a sin.
It's not a sin.
It's not a sin, Sil. It's not.
- Sil!
- Huh?
Nuea.
What happened?
Why did you hang up so quickly?
What are you looking at?
No. Nothing.
Nuea, let's say...
you saw your friend's
friend's boyfriend with...
another woman
who's not your friend's friend.
Would you tell your friend
to tell your friend's friend?
If you're not close to them,
I don't think you should.
They might get into problems
if you misunderstand.
I'm close to them.
It's up to you, then.
If telling them helps you feel better
and is useful to them,
do so.
"I undertake the precept
to refrain from sexual misconduct."
You've got it all wrong.
Why didn't you just ask me?
Would you answer me if I asked?
One hundred percent of cheaters are liars.
So, I asked someone
who would never lie to me.
It's Hia Lian.
He also clarified that
you're really close to Ing-ing Chatchada
and the flight attendant, Aun-aun.
Lian!
You're all here.
Please do me a favor.
Tell Kuea about it.
I know he cares about Kon Diao,
but if it's between Kon Diao and I,
leave it to me.
- You're taking advantage of Kon Diao.
- I know.
- But I...
- Tell him the truth.
You don't like it
when Kon Diao hears your story from others.
I believe it goes the same way.
Lian!
I understand why you don't want to be with me.
But that doesn't mean I'll feel nothing
when I see you're gone.
I dreamed of a tiger,
it terrified me every time.
Will I still see you around when I wake up?