[Warning]
[All incidents in this drama are fictitious.
For entertainment purposes only. Please watch with caution.]
[Present]
[Previously]
You said it yourself. You'll break up with me after getting discharged from the hospital.
When did I promise you that we'll break up?
Where's the evidence? Any document?
It seems that Yi has become a different person
since he lost his memories.
Now,
he is warmer than a microwave oven.
You look fine.
What did you do to dissatisfy Diao?
I don't know. I've lost my memories.
You can't fool me.
It's fine that you don't have to believe that I've really lost my memories.
I will use my amnesia
to find out the truth.
Bulging Eye, I'll catch you to make box meatballs later.
Why do you like to scare it like that?
Even when you have amnesia...
Or...
[Naughty Babe]
You're all here.
Lian.
What's wrong with you?
What's with Kondiao and Kuea's looks?
What did you do to them?
Lian.
The Red Team is Lian Kilen Wang.
His opponent is the Blue Team: Yi Phayak Chatdecha Chen.
Attack!
Lian, go!
Fight.
Time's up. Pause.
Let go first.
The first round is over.
Please.
Don't quarrel first.
Look at what he did.
Yi hit me first.
You two, enough.
Yi hasn't recovered yet.
You shouldn't have stopped them.
Why did you hit me?
Yi Yinyin Anan.
Is Yi crazy?
Yi.
Chatdecha.
Chatchata.
Chatchanok.
Yinyin Anan is my little sister.
Yinyin
Anan
YiYi?
Yes.
But you're the only son.
But my mom remarried.
She didn't use the surname of Chen.
But she's still my mom.
My mom's daughter is my little sister.
Yi.
I knew it.
-I'm sorry. Yi.
-Good.
I was too worried about my friend.
Sorry, Yi. I misunderstood you.
Kondiao, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Just ask me if there is anything you want to know in the future.
Don't trust Lian for everything.
Kuea asked me if you are close.
What did I say wrong?
Lian,
Yi hasn't recovered yet.
Apologize to him.
Hm.
Sorry.
Yi.
I'm really sorry.
I'm begging you.
Please tell Kuea.
I know Kuea is worried about Kondiao.
And you are worried about me.
But I'll take care of the things
between Kondiao and me on my own.
Don't tell anyone about what we've agreed on.
Yi,
please take good care of Kondiao.
Don't scold him.
Let's go, Diao. Let's go home.
Diao,
if you want to know anything in the future, just ask me.
No need to ask others.
There's something I didn't tell you.
Because it's about my dad.
Do you miss your mom?
After my parents divorced,
I can only see my mom twice or three times a month.
With my dad's permission.
My dad is worried about the custody.
That old man doesn't even have time to eat with me.
He doesn't even remember my birthday.
Are you mad at your parents?
I was angry at first.
But I understand.
My dad is busy with work.
He doesn't have much time.
As for my mom,
she remarried and has a new family.
So now I want to fulfill my duty
as a son and a brother.
You must love your mother and little sister, right?
Even though you've lost your memories,
you still remember things about your mother and little sister.
I guess so.
My parents divorced when I started to remember things.
I must have hidden them in my heart.
I have never forgotten them.
But your dad loves you too.
When you were hospitalized,
he was worried about you.
This is what members of the Chen family are like.
Like what?
We don't show our feelings.
Diao,
that's why
it hasn't been easy for you all this time, right?
I'm just not sure
if I'm important to you.
If
you have your memories back
and you remember you don't love me,
will you still be with me?
What if I can never have my memories back?
Will you be with me forever?
If I say
I want to keep loving you,
can I do that?
I love you.
How can I be sure
you love me?
-Because you've lost your memories.
-Diao.
Our memories depend on our brains.
But feelings
depend on our hearts.
This is the information on the investment projects involving Chen's.
As for this bottle of red wine,
it's from Mr. Lian.
Thank you.
Hm.
Mr. Phayak has seen the information on the investment projects involving Chen's.
Yes.
The investment projects involving Chen's.
And Wongteerawit's.
What is Yi doing now?
I'm going to find Yi.
I'll come back to you soon.
You're not lonely. I'll be right back.
Have you received the red wine I gave you?
Yes.
My gift as an apology.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
You already apologized yesterday.
Did you tell Kondiao about everything?
Especially about you pretending to have amnesia.
Not yet.
You said you'd take care of it, right?
This is not the right time.
Yi,
you're at a disadvantage now.
I know.
-But I...
-It's time to tell Kondiao the truth.
You don't like Kondiao to hear about you from others.
Maybe Kondiao thinks the same way.
Give me some more time.
Bye.
Yi, are you busy?
No.
Where is Aon?
Nobody told me you were coming.
I didn't tell anyone.
I just want to see if you're okay.
It still hurts a little.
It still hurts? Then why don't you take a break?
You've lost your memories.
Can you work now?
I have to.
My dad and I are not the only ones in Chen's.
Even though I don't remember,
I have to do it.
You're so stubborn.
Who's the stubborn one?
Huh?
You mean Nong?
Nong is not stubborn.
It's waiting for me to go home.
It's neither stubborn nor naughty. It didn't go anywhere.
The car for the VVIP is here.
Okay.
I'll go there later.
Diao,
come work with me.
I'll only hinder you.
Why would you think like that?
Well,
you haven't taken me with you before.
So I don't think
it's suitable.
It's not that.
I just didn't want to trouble you.
What do you think?
Are you going?
Aren't you here to see if I'm okay?
I can really go, right?
Sure.
Tell me if you don't like it.
I want to go.
Then go get changed.
Okay. Yi.
Three to 74 cars.
Okay.
This is the total number.
This is the total number of this month, right?
Yes, yes.
Okay, I'll take care of it.
Sorry.
Okay.
Hello.
Change this part later. Let me know if anything happens.
Okay.
As usual.
You handle it.
Yes, Boss.
Let's go.
Okay, Yi.
Okay.
Are you tired of it?
No, Yi.
Then
where are we going during the daytime?
Delivering the car to the client
and driving a car to follow it.
Do you have to go in person?
Yes.
If it's a collection car,
not a super sports car assembled in Thailand,
I'll take responsibility if anything goes wrong in the early stage.
Chen's has been recognized by others
because it considers everything for clients
perfectly.
T&P.
Tacha and Phayak, right?
Yes.
This is customized for our engagement.
There are only two pieces.
Well,
it's quite romantic.
Really?
I didn't notice it.
Next time, remove it first.
Okay, Yi.
You like to tease people.
What did I do?
It's all your fault.
Yes, I am here.
Yes.
So... Yeah, today we have a meeting.
Yes, Thursday.
I heard you had a car accident and just got discharged.
And you came to deliver the car personally. I feel guilty.
I've recovered.
You're an important client of Chen's.
How can I not come in person?
Dad, they collided.
Then don't run, kid.
Mr. Kondiao.
Hello, Mr. Chian.
Hello.
Hello, Chun.
Dad, did you ask Mr. Kondiao to see me?
Has Mr. Kondiao already returned from Switzerland?
This is for you.
Thank you.
Mr. Kondiao,
I miss you every day.
Dad told me
he would take me to Switzerland to find you.
Son, Switzerland.
Do you know each other?
You even know he's going to Switzerland?
Kondiao is my son's taekwondo coach.
My son likes Mr. Kondiao very much.
Anyway,
thank you for the high-quality services you've been providing.
Okay.
Mr. Kondiao,
can you move in to live with me?
I want to see you every day.
I can't.
By the way,
since Mr. Kondiao didn't go to Switzerland, where do you live now?
Are you working for the Chen family?
Do you still live at the same place?
The place where the house owner wants to kick you out.
Is that true?
Actually, it was a misunderstanding.
Well.
I want to invite Mr. Kondiao to move to the apartment I bought.
I mean it. Don't stand on ceremony.
And the apartment is close to my company.
I can ask you to help take care of my son when I get off work.
Mr. Chian.
Don't bother, Mr. Chian.
I can take care of my own man myself.
The Chen family
is really good at taking care of employees.
Thoroughly.
I promise
Mr. Yi won't be disappointed.
He may be small,
but he's very diligent.
I have to pick up my son every day.
So I saw Mr. Kondiao ride a bike to teach kids.
Sometimes when he had a tire burst, he had to wheel the bike.
Can Mr. Kondiao stay and play with me?
I have a car toy.
Yes, stay and eat together.
Join us too, Mr. Yi.
It's not very convenient.
Yi.
I don't think you know Kondiao well enough.
Let me introduce him to you first.
This is Kondiao Tacha Wongteerawit. We're engaged.
And we'll get married soon.
Mr. Chian, thank you for supporting the Chen family all this time.
This is
a membership card.
Engaged?
So you're not married.
Soon.
Then I'm taking this opportunity to invite Mr. Chian.
Excuse me.
Bye.
-Yi, about Mr. Chian...
-Leave me alone.
It's okay if you don't want to talk to me now.
But you haven't eaten yet.
I'm not mad at you.
I just don't like it
if they know something that I don't know about you.
I still have amnesia.
I love you.
How can you be sure
you love me?
Wow.
The price is 60 million baht.
Is this a car or an airplane?
Why is it so expensive?
Dad.
Why didn't you answer my call?
Dad, I'm sorry.
Hello.
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
Kondiao has been busy taking care of me.
I don't think he'll have much free time anymore.
Oh. That's great. You should help each other.
I heard about your accident. I was worried about you.
I called Kondiao because I wanted to check on you.
Tem is about to graduate this semester.
He is very interested in cars.
So I want to introduce him
to help Mr. Yi.
Car maintenance.
I just read the report.
The car maintenance business he's responsible for
didn't make any profits last year.
Small enterprises are not doing well.
Right, Tem?
Even my nail salon with Tam
is not doing well either.
Yes, I think we should find a new place.
Actually, I want to do a bigger business.
Car maintenance is just a small business.
I don't have plans to recruit more people.
I'm planning to lay off some workers.
Oh, really?
I still hope you can take care of these younger men.
Kondiao too. Help Mr. Yi with his work.
If you need any help from me and your brother, don't hesitate to let us know.
Okay, Dad.
Excuse me.
Mr. Phayak needs to attend a meeting in 5 minutes.
Oh, you have something to do, right?
We can eat together when Mr. Yi gets better.
I've made a block booking to throw a birthday party at Pentagon.
Kondiao, take Yi with you.
My friends want to see Yi.
-Tam. I think...
-It's not convenient.
I haven't fully recovered. I don't want to go.
Yi, you said you'd give me a sports car.
When can I receive it?
Let me know when you're going to give it to me.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Everything,
including my family
and my misunderstanding of you.
I understand.
I understand why you don't want to live with me.
If you still want to run away from me, I won't blame you.
As long as it can make you feel better.
Yi.
You can have that thought.
I understand.
But it doesn't mean I'm not upset
to see you leave.
Let's get married.
Mr. Tacha Wongteerawit.
[Wongteerawit]
I think your precious son won't listen to us anymore.
He didn't react and didn't help at all.
That's right. I guess Kondiao doesn't want Yi to come to my birthday party.
Hey, Tam.
We went there without making an appointment. Kondiao might be scared.
Right, Dad?
Some of the land of the Formula Racing Circuit
still belongs to us.
Kondiao is still with Yi.
He will help us no matter what.
Taking Kondiao as a hostage is useless.
Nothing can be easily obtained.
The heir of the family had an accident.
They must be more cautious.
Luckily, he's not dead.
Otherwise, Kondiao couldn't get anything.
Actually, they should have married three years ago.
And we could have been able to enjoy our lives long ago.
I wonder what they are waiting for.
Not necessarily.
I don't know what tricks the Chen family will play.
Besides,
your husband once said
Kondiao will inherit half of the Wongteerawit family's land and all of the family's property.
That's good.
We still have time.
Half?
No way.
Tem and Tam are also members of the Wongteerawit family.
That's right.
If it were you, what would you do?
But if it were me,
I wouldn't care about the Wongteerawit family's property.
I have a bigger goal.
Thank you.
For what?
Thank you for not abandoning me.
When I wake up,
will you disappear?
Why are you asking that?
Hm?
I didn't expect
that we could really be together.
I'm here.
Come and sleep here.
Since you came back to live here,
I've slept well every night.
You didn't sleep well?
I often had nightmares.
What nightmares?
I dreamed of a tiger.
The tiger jumped towards me and knocked me down.
I heard someone shouting my name.
Kondiao.
There was blood everywhere.
But it was not my blood.
I was scared.
But I wish you a good dream.
Son,
do you like Mr. Kondiao?
Yes.
I really like Mr. Kondiao.
Well...
I'll invite Mr. Kondiao to accompany you. Okay?
Help! Kondiao. Kondiao.
Uncle! Uncle! Kondiao. Kondiao.
Kondiao.
Don't, Mr. Yi.
Lele is in a bad mood today.
That's just because it wants to go out for a walk.
I dreamed of a tiger. The tiger jumped towards me and knocked me down.
-Kondiao. Kondiao.
-I heard someone shouting my name.
Kondiao.
Kondiao just lost his mom not long ago. I think his memories about his mom are about to disappear.
I'll take full responsibility.
But I wish you a good dream. I was scared.
Yi.
[Preview of the next episode]
Dad, why would the Chen family help us?
Aren't you living happily and comfortably?
That's enough.
I'm not sure what my dad knows
or what he wants from the Chen family.
Even if they get married,
nothing can guarantee that we can get more money from the Chen family.
We must.
If anything happens to Kondiao this time,
I'll really kick you out of this family.
You gave up my mom. I think I can put up with that.
Or should I really give him up?
You have regained your memories, right?
["Naughty Babe" (Uncut Version) only available on the iQIYI app and iQ.com]