[Warning]
[All incidents in this drama are fictitious.
It is for entertainment purposes only. Please watch with caution.]
[Sponsored by the following brands]
[Previously]
I'm begging you.
Please tell Kuea too.
I know Kuea is worried about Kondiao.
But I'll take care of things between Kondiao and me myself.
You're using Kondiao now.
-I know, but I...
-You can tell Kondiao the truth now.
You don't want Kondiao to know about you from others, do you?
Kondiao probably doesn't like it either.
Lian.
I know you don’t want to be with me.
But it doesn't mean I'm happy to see you leave.
I dreamed of a tiger.
Every time I dreamed of it,
I was scared.
Will you disappear when I wake up?
Ah!
[Naughty Babe]
[Yi Phayak Chatdecha Chen]
[Played by Kornthas Rujeerattanavorapan]
[Kondiao Tacha Wongteerawit]
[Played by Nat Natasitt Uareksit]
[Kuea Keerati]
[Lian Kilen Wang]
[Played by Chawarin Perdpiriyawong]
[Played by Pruk Panich]
[Played by Sin Samoe Pharinyakorn Khansawa]
[Played by Neua Kathakat Lamnoi]
[Secretary Oon, played by Supha Sangarawong]
[Played by Makorn Penphet Penkul]
[Played by Sattha Teerapong Leowrakwong]
[Played by Sathaporn Tawatson Plengsiriwat]
[Stepmother, played by Orn Thanyaporn Sontikan]
[Screenplay by Kanyapat Jitrattanaarun (BamBam)] [Screenplay by crewave
Piangpaitoon Satrawaha
Preechaya Prayongsap]
[Directed by Kittipat Champa]
[Co-directed by Nathavat Piyapong]
[Naughty Babe]
Diao.
Thank you.
I've recovered.
You still have me.
I'm here.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll protect you.
No matter what troubles you have in your mind,
just let them go.
If you can't,
you can share some with me.
Let me be your shelter.
Thank you. You're awesome.
-Not at all. I'm not awesome.
You are.
I pretended to be awesome...
I pretended to be awesome
because I wanted to look after you.
But in reality, I have many flaws.
No one is perfect. Yi.
Don't think you're not good enough.
I want you to treat yourself better.
You don't have to always take care of and protect me.
I'm not a seven-year-old anymore.
Earlier,
did I make you worry?
No.
I was not worried
but not being sure.
And it was very difficult for me.
Because I didn't know
whether you took care of me
out of your need
or because you had to do this.
Yi.
Does it hurt?
I'll get you the medical kit.
Diao.
Stay still.
Yi.
I can handle it myself.
Don't move.
Does it still hurt?
No, thanks.
I don't want to see you get hurt.
I'd rather get hurt myself.
What about the wound on your face?
It's okay.
It's just a minor injury. I don't feel anything.
Do you think it's cool?
Thank you.
It's not only about the wound,
but also about us.
What do you mean?
If it's about what we just talked about,
my answer is no.
Everything I did for you,
I never did it because it was necessary.
I did it all because of you.
Just because of me?
Yes.
Just because of you.
Ask me again.
What?
Even though I may not remember it.
Yes.
Even if you still can't remember,
whether it's about my family
or that you thought I was running away,
if you ask me again,
I'll answer you this time.
Tacha Wongteerawit.
Will you marry Phayak Chatdecha Chen?
I do.
Puppy, Diao is here for you.
Let me hug you.
Diao.
Yes, Yi.
Bulging Eye.
You call it that again?
Its eyes are not bulging at all.
It's just they are big.
Before you lost your memory,
you liked to call it Bulging Eye, too.
I just named it after its appearance.
Really?
You said you remembered everything,
but you pretended that you had lost your memory, did you?
Why would I do that?
Have a good time in your work. Yi.
Diao, aren't you coming?
No, I have something to do.
About things you wanted to know last night...
It's okay. We can talk about that when it's convenient for you.
Bye. Yi.
Can you tell me?
Is there anything else I don't know?
About you,
your family,
and my family.
Were we close when we were kids?
Why do you ask?
Because you said you remembered me when I was seven.
What do you want to know?
Go ahead and ask.
I'll tell you.
I trust you.
But it's late now.
Shall we go to sleep?
I'm sleepy.
Diao.
Yes?
If you have a nightmare some night,
just turn around and hug me.
You too.
Let's go to sleep, okay?
I'm sleepy.
I want the quilt too.
How can you be so mischievous when you're hurt? Naughty babe.
I'm not mischievous at all.
I'm just naughty.
Yi.
Boss, you're getting married?
Is that true?
I've never made a joke.
It's true.
Really? Really?
You're not as fun as my husband.
Can you get the preparation work done within three weeks?
Yes.
Okay, thank you.
Especially you, Ms. Kim.
Don't let me down since you've been married.
But...
There's a tiny problem, Boss.
I forgot. Are you worried about your kid?
She's just a baby girl. I won't have time during Christmas.
Boss.
I haven't been on my honeymoon.
Then I'm counting on you, Don.
I'm willing to help.
Don't forget that we can't trust anyone yet.
At this ceremony, Kondiao's safety is the most important.
Yes, Sir.
Okay, Boss.
I have something important to tell you.
Mr. Phayak is getting married in three weeks.
Can you tell me
if there's anything else I don't know?
About you, your family, and my family.
[Dad]
[Kondiao]
What's wrong? Why are you calling me today?
Dad. Are you busy? I want to talk to you.
-It's that I...
-We can talk anytime.
We're not in different time zones like when you were in the UK.
Dad.
Why did you send me to the UK?
I wanted to give you the best thing.
At that time, the UK was the best choice.
Whether in terms of chances or connections.
And a sponsor like the Chen family would support you.
Then why did the Chen family help us?
I don't want to talk about it. It's been a long time.
That's right.
That's why I want to know why.
I only knew
you would have a good place to live
and a good school to study at.
That was enough.
I didn't have any more wishes.
I just hoped you could come back after you finished your study
and help the Wongteerawit family. That's all.
How can I help the Wongteerawit family?
When do you want me to come home and help?
Don't bother.
You are helping the family by just staying there.
What do you take me for?
You are happy there, aren't you?
You know nothing.
You and Yi are engaged.
You're part of the Chen family.
What kind of attitude are you still putting on?
Or
did you fight with Yi?
He doesn't know.
Tam said you didn't want to help the family.
Did Tam say that?
Are you on the phone?
But I didn't say that.
Diao.
Well... Uncle Sathaporn is here to talk to me.
We'll talk later.
I love you.
Were you talking to Diao? Is something wrong?
No, we were just talking about the past.
The past?
Why don't you tell him? Why do you hide from him?
We had a deal that we wouldn't talk about this anymore.
Don't worry about it anymore.
Okay.
Well...
Did he tell you about the wedding?
Whose wedding?
Oh.
It's Diao and Phayak's.
Is Kondiao getting married?
I didn't know at all.
No wonder.
He called and said something strange.
He was probably too shy to tell me.
You can call him back and talk to him.
It's okay.
Let's talk about our business first.
Are you here
to get the materials for the Formula Racing venue?
Thank you.
As for the parts business,
I would like to set it aside for now.
I don't have any money these days.
Then how long do you want to postpone it?
It should be after Diao and Yi's wedding.
But even if they get married,
there's no guarantee that we can get more money from the Chen family.
Unless
we can get more from the engagement agreement.
Of course, we can.
I forgot.
Makorn likes Kondiao very much.
Before they get married,
we must sign a new contract with them.
We need to make clear about the bridal gifts,
especially
the share of the formula racing venue.
If possible, don't forget me, your brother.
I won't.
We've been through thick and thin together.
Anyway, the Wongteerawit family will be thrived again.
Should I prepare a celebration party?
7 years old.
Wongteerawit.
The Chen family.
[7 years old; Wongteerawit; The Chen family]
Chen's Mansion.
Tiger. Tiger accident.
[Chen’s Mansion; Tiger]
In my dream...
Diao.
The nightmares.
You would have a good place to live
and a good school to study at.
That was enough.
Went to England.
[Nightmares; Went to England]
You and Yi are engaged.
You're part of the Chen family.
You're helping the family just by staying there.
I love you.
[7 years old]
It's okay.
Yi.
I know where it is.
I'll call you back later.
Diao, what's wrong?
What happened?
I don't know what happened.
I don't know what to do.
Diao.
Raise your head and talk to me, okay?
I'm here.
I don't know what happened.
It seems that I know nothing.
Why do I...
What do you not know?
I called my dad
to figure out what happened.
I want to arrange everything well.
I know my dad treats me as a bargaining chip to negotiate with you and your dad.
He said he loved me.
But if he really loves me,
why did he...
I really want to believe that my dad loves me.
It's okay.
It's okay, Diao.
Yi, you were willing to compromise with my dad
because there was me, right?
Would it be better if you weren't
with me?
Phayak's car is undergoing a thorough reexamination at Chen's factory.
The bodyguards have been replaced. They're all Phayak's bodyguards now.
Mr. Tem, you'd better figure it out yourself.
Uncle, what should we do?
The Chen family got the car.
What are you doing?
If we don't say anything, who will know? Didn't you do everything as I said?
How can I be sure...
Did you check the CCTV?
Where's?
No one saw me at the hospital.
Wait.
Did you go to the hospital?
When did you go?
Mr. Aon.
What's the matter?
When I found out that Yi had a car accident.
But the Chen family didn't allow anyone to visit him.
Kim.
I don't know. Uncle, you must help me.
I won't admit that I did it alone.
If you don't help me, I'll tell Dad.
Don't you want to get Wongteerawit?
If you tell your dad, what's your mom going to do? Have you thought about that?
Stay still. Don't panic.
I'll take care of it.
Yi.
What's wrong?
I'm not sure
what my dad knows
or what he wants from the Chen family.
To be honest,
I can't stand that Wongteerawit benefited from the Chen family in this way.
And I know
your dad and you compromised
because of me.
Diao, what do you know?
Yi, what about you? What do you know?
You don't know anything.
Or are you just pretending?
Your memories are back, right?
I want to pretend.
Can you speak louder?
I want to pretend that I don't know anything.
I...
Since when?
Since I woke up.
I really lost my memory.
You said you only remembered me when I was seven.
Yes.
I really lost my memory then.
But when I woke up again,
I remembered everything in the past.
It's just that the things that happened the day before waking up
were chaotic.
But I remembered it after a while.
I knew we didn't break off the engagement
and I had never been with anyone else.
And I never wanted you to leave me.
But I almost killed you.
-Diao.
-In your life,
I let this happen.
If you were born without me,
you might be able to live a different life that you want
and you don't have to be restrained by your guilt about the past.
Yi.
Let's not get married.
Diao, no.
Or do you still want to go to Switzerland?
It has nothing to do with that.
I don't know. Wherever you go, I'll follow you.
I won't let you leave me again.
Please.
It was my fault all this time.
I didn't want to tell you
how I feel.
But now I'm willing to.
Diao, don't leave again.
But if that's the case,
we'll always be trapped in this situation.
I really don't want to stay here like this anymore.
Diao. What do you want me to do?
As long as you tell me,
I'll do everything for you.
Yi. Do you trust me?
Then let's
ruin our wedding, okay?
Aren't you too late?
You just got the car's examination report.
Yi, your car fell over.
You almost died, yet you're still so slow.
I'll take care of it.
Dad, why are you worried? I can handle it myself.
If you had solved it from the start,
this wouldn't have happened.
What?
Your car was parked at home, but you let someone else tamper with it.
You made a mistake this time.
I'm good enough that I didn't kick you out of our family business.
Hey, give it to your boss
to see if there's anything in common.
Diao.
Is there any other car at home under Diao's name?
No.
This is the only one under Mr. Tacha's name.
What about the usage record?
Mr. Tacha only used it when Lian drove.
It's recorded that
Mr. Tacha's driving coach said Mr. Tacha was afraid to drive
because cars went fast.
So when he went out, he would ride a bike
or take a BTS.
Diao is fine
because he rode a bike instead of driving the car I bought.
You really take good care of Diao.
Who else knows
that car belongs to Diao?
Only us.
And Wongteerawit.
[Wongteerawit]
Why did the Chen family help us?
That's why I want to know why you did that.
What can I do to help Wongteerawit?
What do you take me for?
[Son. Why didn't you tell me that you were going to get married?]
Aon.
Go check everything immediately.
The car remains, the CCTV cameras at home, the exhibition hall, and the factory which helped with the registration,
including people related to these documents.
Yes, Boss.
Dad.
I'll handle this myself.
Their target is not me,
but Diao.
You know what? The problem now is not only personal damage and property loss.
What matters is they want Diao's life.
Yi.
Everything I have is yours.
If it helps you, you should use it.
I've raised you to be wise, strong, respectful, and dignified.
I didn't raise you to be stupid, rigid, and don't show your weakness, you know?
I'll give you time until the wedding day.
Find out who did this. I'll take care of the rest.
And take care of Diao for me.
If anything happens to Diao this time, even if it's a little toe,
I'll kick you out of the Chen family. Go!
Dad.
Or should I let Diao go?
Yi, do you want to live a life like mine?
If you were willing to let Mom go,
I think I can bear letting Diao go.
I didn't let her go. She left on her own.
She didn't love me anymore.
Yi. You can live like me.
When there's a chance, do whatever you can.
If you love someone,
you should let him know.
-But I've made many mistakes.
-You've grown up.
Be confident.
Son, I'm proud of you.
There's only one thing left,
which is I can only close my eyes
after I see your wish come true.
Then don't die.
If you die now, I will...
Brat.
Kondiao doesn't want to marry me.
Brat. Get out of my house!
Go.
Don't come back.
What happened between you and your dad?
Nothing.
Dad was just afraid that I wouldn't marry Diao.
Then why did you come to me?
Wongteerawit didn't want to kill me.
He wanted to kill Diao.
What did Diao say?
Diao doesn't know yet.
You're hiding it from him again.
I don't know what to say.
It could be someone else.
His stepmother, half-brother or sister.
But if they are all Diao's father's children...
Diao will find out eventually.
I just don't want Diao to be disappointed anymore.
Yi, no matter what, you can't stop Diao from finding out the truth.
Besides,
Kondiao is not that fragile.
He can even defeat me.
Uh.
I just want to handle everything well before telling him.
If he comes up with something, and asks me,
just like when he ran away to Switzerland, that'll be a big problem.
I just want Diao to focus on ruining our wedding.
Ruin the wedding?
Your wedding with Kondiao?
Yes, my wedding with Diao.
Kondiao.
Do you need me to drive you home? You can put your bike in my car.
No, thanks.
I can ride my bike back.
But
it's dangerous for you to drive like this.
You can go back now.
But...
-I'm worried about you.
-Don't worry.
I can take care of myself.
Be careful on your way back.
[Standby]
This one follows me.
That one also follows me.
What a tight schedule.
Boss. I think Mr. Tacha already noticed. He left by bike.
Why do you come back so late?
The father of the kid I teach taekwondo followed me.
Is he chasing you?
I don't know.
Then you have to say no right away. What if he becomes a stalker?
I remember that Yi also sent a bodyguard to follow me.
Why?
Wait, Yi is calling.
Hello, Yi.
Hello, Kondiao. Where are you? What are you doing? Why didn't you pick up the phone?
I told you to tell me where you would go.
Wait, I couldn't catch them in time.
I'm worried about you.
I'm fine.
Let me see what you look like when you're worried.
Can you see me clearly?
Where are you now?
I'm at Kuea's house. I'm with Kuea.
Yes, Yi.
Don't worry about Kondiao. I'll take care of him.
Diao, I'll be late tonight.
I'm here to talk to Lian.
What is it?
You can go home to Kondiao.
I want to go home now.
I miss Kuea.
I miss you too.
Kuea.
Enough. Go elsewhere and say that you miss him. I want to talk to Diao.
Yi. Anything else?
I'll pick you up two hours later. Is it okay?
I can go home by myself.
No, it's late and dangerous.
Let me pick you up.
You can ask someone to pick me up.
Sleep here tonight, Kondiao.
I don't permit it. See you at home. Diao.
Okay, Yi.
Have a good talk with Lian.
See you at home. Yi.
Bye.
Yi.
No matter what, you will marry Kondiao, right?
Yes.
Kuea.
I need your help.
Why don't you oppose him?
Do you think I won't?
You were willing to be the victim
and asked Wongteerawit to make it up to you
because Kondiao wanted to cancel the wedding?
Yes.
Are you serious?
I wasn't so sure before.
Hide.
I don't care where I go. I'll just hide for a while.
Let them see me as a loser.
You, loser?
Are you sure you won't regret it?
It's fun.
Kuea doesn't like you either.
Never.
You must get married. Don't hold onto any lucky thoughts anymore.
My groomsman attire is ready.
Protect Kuea. Because no matter what happens to Diao,
Kuea Keerati is involved.
I'll do my best to help you.
Deal. As your friend, I will always say yes to you.
[Executive director Aoftionz] [Co-executive director Kiaryder]
[Work: Bam Bam]
Has Kondiao ever complained to you or discussed wedding matters with you?
Did Yi ask you to find out?
I don't think you can avoid it no matter what.
Why do you want to ruin your own wedding?
-I want to fight, but I don't know who the enemy is.
-Coach, you don't seem happy.
Before you go to Switzerland,
if you feel depressed,
just walk out.
It's all because of that, right?
That matter has linked our two families.
Diao lost her childhood memory because of me.
In order to get what they want,
everyone uses Diao as a condition.
Diao, do whatever you want. If this wedding is like an act,
let's play every scene well.
From now on, I will create
your happiness for you.