[Warning]
[All incidents in this drama are fictitious.
It is for entertainment purposes only. Please watch with caution.]
[Previously]
Dad, why would the Chen family help us?
You're happy, right?
That's enough.
I'm not sure what you know
or what you want from the Chen family.
Even if they get married,
we can't guarantee that we can get more money from the Chen family.
We can invest.
If anything happens to Diao this time,
I'll really kick you out of the Chen family.
You let my mom go. I think I can continue to put up with it.
Maybe I should let him go.
Yi, have you regained your memories?
[Naughty Babe]
[Yi Phayak Chatdecha Chen]
[Played by Kornthas Rujeerattanavorapan]
[Kondiao Tacha Wongteerawit]
[Played by Nat Natasitt Uareksit]
[Kuea Keerati]
[Lian Kilen Wang]
[Played by Chawarin Perdpiriyawong]
[Played by Pruk Panich]
[Pharinyakorn Khansawa acts as Sin Samoe]
[Kathakat Lamnoi acts as Neua]
[Supha Sangarawong acts as Secretary Oon]
[Penphet Penkul acts as Makorn]
[Teerapong Leowrakwong acts as Sattha]
[Tawatson Plengsiriwat acts as Sathaporn]
[Thanyaporn Sontikan acts as Orn, the stepmother]
[Executive Producer Mandee Work]
[Supervised by Sunanda Sota]
[Producer Thanaporn Puangpat]
[Director of Photography 1 Sarawut Chuphakpanich]
[Director of Photography 2 Nithiwat Samanlah]
[Director of Photography 3 Panpho Boonprasert]
[Assistant to Director 1 Noraphon Limwongrujirat]
[Assistant to Director 2 Kesinee Thitiananpakorn]
[Performance Director: Nathawar Piyanonphong]
[Costume Design Purimphat Nithiwatsophon]
[Scene Design Bannokkawao Artfilm]
[Art Director Patcharaphon Chantharamit]
[Assistant to Art Director Atikhun Petkratok]
[Post-production Director Nonthacharn Prakobsap]
[Director of Photography Prayung Panngam]
[Compositor Klaokawin Trithipayarak]
[Screenwriter: Kanyapat Jitrattanaarun
Piangpaitoon Satrawaha]
[Assistant to Screenwriter: Preechaya Prayongsap]
[Director Kittipat Champa]
[Joint Director Nathavat Piyapong]
[Naughty Babe]
Why is it so expensive?
It would be better if we don't have a wedding, right?
And he doesn't have to pay so much.
No.
If that's the case, his plan of losing memories
will be in vain.
I'm back.
Are you okay, Yi?
Use the nasal inhaler first.
I'm going to get you some water.
Wait.
I'm good.
I'm fine.
I'm not drunk either.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at the catalogue made by the designer.
It was finished a long time ago.
I'm gonna take a look too.
Yi, it's late.
Why don't you go wash up and sleep?
I can
look at this tomorrow morning.
Do you want to look at it alone?
Don't you want me to look at it with you?
You don't trust my taste. Is that it?
It's not like that.
This was finished long ago.
But I've never seen you look at it.
I thought you weren't interested in this.
It's not that I'm not interested.
Back then, I wanted you to choose what you like.
Besides,
I'm jealous.
Really?
My bad.
I didn't tell you my thoughts.
That's why you misunderstood me.
I didn't ask you, Yi.
I was worried that you might dislike me.
So it was my fault too.
From now on, let's communicate more.
Okay?
Okay.
Let's choose together, okay?
Yi.
Can I ask you some questions?
Of course.
Didn't we just agree
to communicate more?
When I was 7,
you and I...
I remember I was happy
because my dad took me to a big house.
I had a playmate.
He's a very kind brother.
How much do you remember?
I remember the big house
had a butterfly wind chime in front of the door.
There was a big garden in the house.
I was playing with you.
You disappeared.
Then I saw a tiger.
Lele.
It was my tiger.
I was going to take it to you,
but it escaped.
I thought I could keep an eye on it.
The person who looked after the tiger warned me.
Even though your body wasn't hurt,
your heart was hurt badly.
You've lost your childhood memories because of me.
Even if I take care of you for the rest of your life,
I can't make up for what you've been through.
Lele was taken away.
It was all my fault.
Yi,
I'm sorry.
If I weren't there that day...
Diao,
you shouldn't have said sorry.
I,
my dad,
and Wongtheerawit should apologize.
We made you like this.
That accident
is the reason for everything today.
Everyone thinks this is for your good.
To get what they want,
they treat you as a tool.
I'm sorry.
From today on,
let me make you happy.
Where is my happiness?
I want you to be happy too.
Let me
make you happy.
Today,
let me make you happy.
Let me "take care of" you.
It won't hurt.
Kuea,
did Kondiao complain to you or negotiate with you about the wedding?
Did Yi ask you to ask about it?
No.
I'm just worried.
People may think too much before the wedding,
especially Kondiao.
Why are you worried about that?
They will get married anyway.
Diao has been waiting for 3 years.
I don't think it'll go wrong no matter what.
Did you say "go wrong"?
I was just saying.
Nothing.
Just confess.
What's the plan of you and Kondiao?
Nothing.
I don't have a plan.
Really?
Why are you so close to me?
Do you want me to give you a facial massage?
Fine.
Kuea,
didn't you say you would tell me everything?
Are you hiding something from me?
Do you really want me to do "something good" to you before you tell me?
You're making me sad.
Lian,
I really can't tell you.
I promised Kondiao.
Look.
You really have a plan.
Have you realized your mistake?
I love you,
but I love Kondiao too.
I won't tell you no matter what you do.
Hm.
You are so stubborn.
I'm really gonna get angry.
You'll be happy after I coax you.
Mr. Kuea Keerati, you're too confident.
Mr. Kilen, don't think that I'll do everything as you say.
Did you do as I said?
But seriously,
if anything goes wrong with the plan of you and Kondiao,
I hope you can stay out of their business.
Are you saying I'm nosy?
That's not what I meant.
I just want to say they should deal with their own problems.
Have you heard about this?
They say people who lie in bed and chat
are different from those who sit and chat.
Then how long are you going to sit and chat with me?
Let's lie down and chat, okay?
Kuea.
Don't change the topic. I'm really worried about you.
Humph.
You're not worried about me.
You're more worried about your friend.
Why?
You're just worried that Kondiao's plan will succeed, right?
Why are you getting worse, little Annabel?
Let's make a bet.
Just for fun.
The one who loses has to listen to the winner.
Kuea, we shouldn't make a bet on our friends' life for fun.
Then let's be serious.
To be honest, considering what Kondiao has felt and what he wants,
he's not joking with Yi.
Fine.
Annabel, just wait. You'll lose.
Lian.
Enough.
I don't want to drink a lot today.
Why? Are you under a lot of pressure?
We need to be more careful these days.
The Chen family is investigating things about Wongtheerawit.
Investigating?
Investigating what?
I don't know.
But it'll be bad if they find out about us during the investigation.
How can they find it out?
It's been over 20 years.
And most importantly,
that old man doesn't know yet.
My brother is a fool,
but Makorn is not stupid.
You have to be careful.
Besides,
we need to keep a distance from each other these days.
Should we separate?
How long?
At least
we have to wait until the Chen family writes a new agreement to negotiate.
A marriage agreement?
Yes.
Then we can get a lot of benefits.
Let's lay low for a while.
Soon,
everything of Wongtheerawit and the Chen family will be ours.
You know what? You're not the only one who had nightmares about that day.
I couldn't sleep either.
Did you start to have nightmares from that day on?
Was it because of me?
I told you it wasn't because of you.
I was just a kid back then.
I was very scared.
I've been hiding what happened that day in my heart till today.
Is that when the torture started?
I'm telling you this
because I don't want you
to be worried when you see I can't fall asleep.
I don't want you to be burdened with it
or think about it alone.
But if this is the problem...
Let's solve it together.
Okay.
Yi, I want to know one more thing.
What is it?
Is this all because of that?
Is that why the two families are intertwined?
After what happened that day,
you almost died because of me.
You lost your memories.
My dad wanted to be responsible for everything and make it up to your family.
So he drafted the cooperation agreement between the two families.
It involves business
and what the Chen family has to be responsible for.
Responsible for everything?
What does it include?
Medical expenses,
compensation,
and child care expenses.
Is there anything else after we were engaged?
Just monthly living expenses.
The agreement has additional terms.
That's why my dad used me to gain benefits from the Chen family.
I'm fine now.
Why should you pay?
What about my trip to the U.K.?
Was it my dad?
No.
My dad wanted to make you break up with your family
and wait for the benefits.
Yi, tell me.
Has my dad ever loved me?
Thank you
for always protecting me.
Diao.
Thank you
for not letting go of me.
I won't be controlled by Wongtheerawit anymore.
I want to have my own life.
I don't want to be a Wongtheerawit member anymore.
Do you want to be a member of the Chen family?
Before you become a member of the Chen family,
why don't we take a shower?
Okay.
What are you doing?
If you have something good, you should share it with me.
Is this your good thing?
Are you sure it's not a water bottle?
You're just on the top. It doesn't mean you're the best.
Maybe others can also do what you can do.
What are you talking about, Tam?
Dad.
I told you
not to touch the wine.
They are expensive.
Dad, you put the wine here. If they are not for drinking, why did you put them here?
Idiot. The longer you put them, the more expensive they are.
Right, Dad?
It's okay. Let him be.
You need to tell me if you want to drink next time.
I don't like sneaky people.
Okay.
Dad, I said I want to invest in that brand.
How's it going?
I haven't thought about that yet.
I've been busy
with Kondiao's things.
Think about it as soon as possible.
The price is just right.
If I don't buy it now, I might miss the chance.
Okay, I'll transfer it to you tomorrow.
Really? Thank you, Dad.
I love you the most.
Have you made money from her designer bags?
Let her be.
She's also working to support herself.
What about my car maintenance business?
How about this?
Ask your brother to talk to Yi first.
Ask him to help. You go explain everything.
That's all I can do for you.
Yi, don't mess with my stuff.
Kondiao,
why did you put things in the box?
Why don't you display them?
To whom?
Just put them here.
You won a competition, right?
Don't you feel proud?
I can just put the sense of pride in my heart.
I plan to quit anyway.
Do you plan to go to Switzerland to raise cows?
I don't think I'll really go there to raise cows.
I'll go there to take a look first
and see what I can do.
If you don't go to Switzerland,
stay in Thailand,
and abandon everything,
what do you want to do?
In terms of a job,
I love being a coach.
I like being with kids.
If I have more time to practice,
I want to get the Level 5 certificate.
Okay.
Just do it.
Can I?
Yes.
I will help you
accomplish everything you want to do.
As long as you ask,
I will do everything for you.
Yi.
Because I love you.
I won't hide it.
I want you to see it every minute.
Don't hide it in the box.
And I hope you can allow me
to see
what else is in your heart.
There's something I...
I have been hiding.
What is it?
Love.
What is it again?
I didn't hear it.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I love you too.
Everyone, line up.
I have something to tell you today.
What I want to say is...
is...
Mr. Kondiao is back.
I'm back for you.
Welcome.
All right, everyone.
Let's keep practicing hard.
Line up.
Attention.
Bow.
Ready.
Horse stance.
One.
One punch.
-One.
-Ah.
Two.
Ah.
Three.
Four.
Ah.
Five.
Ready.
Good job, everyone.
Mr. Kondiao.
Mr. Chian.
Have you come back to teach again?
Yes, I just came back today.
Does that mean you'll come often?
I'm not sure.
I think so. They need a teacher today.
The school contacted me and asked me to come back to teach.
Then I'll be honest with you.
I asked the school to contact you and ask you to come back to teach.
After we met in my house last time,
Chun kept crying and looking for you.
So I asked Mr. Winner to contact you.
I'm glad you came back to teach.
And...
I almost lost my hope.
Okay.
Mr. Kondiao. Dad.
Chun.
Dad, Mr. Kondiao taught me today.
It was great, right?
Yes, Dad. It was great. Mr. Kondiao is amazing.
Then let's invite Mr. Kondiao to have a meal together. What do you think?
Okay.
Mr. Kondiao.
Can you go have a meal with me?
I can't go.
I have to go home and eat with the man I'm engaged to.
It was fine in the past.
Or are you worried that Mr. Yi might scold you?
Should I call him?
It's not like that.
You don't look happy at all.
You didn't look happy either before going to Switzerland.
If you feel upset and uncomfortable,
just come out.
Let's go.
I found a new Omakase Japanese restaurant. It has Japanese chefs.
They have great cooking skills.
You misunderstood.
I'm very happy now.
The only place I want to go back for dinner
is my home where Yi is waiting for me.
Excuse me.
Then why do you want to go to Switzerland?
Are you sure you are happy now?
Don't think I'm nosy.
I can see that.
You can be happier than now.
It depends on whether you're willing to open your heart.
Yes.
I've opened my heart.
Only Yi can walk into my heart.
If I have to make a choice
between opening my heart to someone else and living without Yi,
I will choose to live without Yi.
Because Yi is my source of happiness. Not everyone can do that.
Sorry.
Aon, help me handle my work schedule.
If a representative can do my work, ask a representative to do it.
Cancel all my social activities with my friends.
I want to spend more time with Kondiao.
The wedding is the top priority.
Okay, Boss.
I'm gonna call Mr. Lian to cancel the appointment at Pentagon tonight.
No. The appointment tonight is very important.
I have to meet Lian. In terms of other things, do as I said.
Thank you.
Okay, Boss.
Oh.
Didn't he say he'd come back to have dinner together?
Hello, Yi.
When will you come back tonight?
I have something to talk with Lian at Pentagon.
Okay.
What a pity. You missed.
My arm hurts.
Really?
I was just going to praise you for doing a good job.
Watch your mouth.
Be careful.
Come on.
Show me.
Like this?
Brag when you can do it, stupid Yi.
Stupid Lian, you're really good at bragging.
Why have I made friends with someone who's good at bragging like you?
Because you love me, bro.
More precisely,
I'm your only friend.
I have other friends.
But no one can share wisdom with you like me.
Thank you very much.
Of course. Do you know why you have a friend like me?
Why?
Because you're stupid, stupid Yi.
Stupid Lian. Why did you swear at me for no reason?
Because you are stupid.
And you still won't admit it.
If you didn't have a friend like me, you wouldn't have gone this far.
What are you trying to say?
-Just say it.
-What are you thinking? You plan to ruin your wedding.
I have to do it.
It won't be a problem even if you plan to do it.
The point is you have to figure out who your enemy is.
If you plan to fight, but you don't know your enemy,
you'll only fail.
How can I not know?
I've known Kondiao for more than 20 years.
Then do you know
who Kondiao has invited to be his best men?
Kuea.
Not just Kuea.
See?
I told you you're stupid, stupid Yi.
Who?
Kondiao's best men are
AKA Ironman Gang.
They are...
The last one, Kirin,
is a world-renowned artist worth $15 million.
Enough, Lian. I don't want to hear you flatter your lover.
Why do Kondiao have four best men?
What about me? Who do I have?
When something like this happens, I want to quit being your friend.
No way.
You have to stay and help me.
[Okay, everyone. Our plan is top-secret. Don't tell anyone else.]
Especially Lian.
[Especially Yi.]
What, Kuea?
You're defending Lian again.
This is quite interesting.
Let them think we know nothing first.
And then we can launch a counterattack on these naughty kids.
Kondiao and Kuea must be taught a lesson.
Let them know
they can't be naughty in front of us.
Okay. Ready.
Look at the camera.
Good. Three, 2.
Smile.
One, 2.
Smile. Three, 2.
Very handsome.
Mr. Phayak, smile.
Please wait a moment.
Yi, do tigers not smile easily?
I think I smiled.
No, your expression was like this.
Me? No way.
Really.
You looked like you were forced here to take photos.
If I display the photos,
people will think you are forced to get married.
I'm not good at it.
Let's do it again.
Okay.
Everyone.
We are ready.
Ready.
Smile. Three, 2.
Three, 2.
Mr. Phayak, a bigger smile please.
Yi, it's not natural at all.
If you can't do it, try to say "cheese", okay?
"Cheese"?
"Cheese".
You want me to do it?
Yi, it's easy. Use your fingers like this. "Cheese".
-It's not difficult at all. "Cheese".
-"Cheese".
Yi, you look cute like this.
"Cheese".
We're ready.
Okay.
One, 2.
"Cheese".
Okay, let's call it a day. Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Yi,
my friends and I will have a bachelor party at Kuea's place tonight.
Let me take you there.
Oh. It's okay.
I can go by myself.
Are you going to ride a bike again?
I'll pick you up.
Yi, it's okay.
I don't know when it'll be over.
Yi, have a good rest.
I'm worried about you.
Don't worry about me.
Just tonight.
After this, I won't go to any party anymore.
This is what you said about pretending we're really getting married, right?
Whatever.
Do whatever you want.
You sound like you don't want me to go.
It's just a bachelor party.
It's really nothing.
You should know what it is.
If this marriage is like a play,
let's do our best in every scene.
Everyone,
listen.
Once the music is played,
this door will open.
We take Yi to the hall.
When the door opens,
Yi will say "oh, Kondiao".
"Where is Kondiao"?
And the guests will start to panic. While they are panic,
Winner, Jiew,
go to the door and lock the door. Bang.
And In, take this opportunity
to run to the power supply room and cut off electricity in the whole building.
After the power is cut off, bang,
Kondiao,
it'll be your turn.
Run to the elevator
and go to the roof.
When you arrive at the roof, go to the heliport.
I'll wait for you there.
What do you think? Is my plan cool?
The elevator won't be available if the power is cut off.
Also,
there will be bodyguards and security guards of the Chen family everywhere
at the wedding.
There are only five of us. This is a big plan. I don't think it will work.
Haha. In the end, Kondiao still has to go back and get married.
What do you mean?
Why did you let me talk for so long?
I thought my plan was great.
Who else can come up with another plan?
Kondiao, what do you think? Do you have an idea?
Kondiao.
Are you listening? I'm asking you.
That's good.
Let's do it according to this plan.
Let me talk to Kondiao.
You have to pull yourself together.
What's on your mind?
I'm not sure.
Not sure?
Are you worried that the plan won't work?
No.
I'm worried about Yi.
I'm afraid if the plan succeeds,
Yi will be very sad.
I don't know which is the right choice.
Should I marry Yi or leave him quietly?
I don't have to go to Switzerland.
I can go somewhere else.
I can go somewhere further than that place,
and it will be harder to find me.
But what will happen to Yi?
Kuea, I'm worried that Yi will be heart-broken.
It's okay.
Take your time.
There must be a way.
[Executive Director Aoftionz
Joint Executive Director Kiaryder
Production: Bam Bam]
[Preview of the next episode]
Dad, the Chen family has given too much compensation to Wongteerawit.
I'll protect Yi too.
The easiest way to ruin the wedding is for me to run away.
If you want to run away as you've planned,
you have to escape from my men first.
If Kondiao's plan is good, I'll pretend I know nothing.
You have to make sure nothing will go wrong.
Someone has been following me for a while.
I finally got rid of them.
Dad, you need more bodyguards here. Maybe I'm not the only one who has been followed.
I won't do that.
They're brothers.
No matter what the reason is or who he is,
it won't make a difference even if he's Kondiao's biological father.
I won't let Kondiao suffer anymore.