Warning: All occurrences happened
in this series are fictional
and for an entertainment purpose only.
Viewer discretion required.
Did Kon Diao complain about the wedding
or discuss it with you?
Did Hia Yi send you to investigate me?
I don't think it'll ever be canceled.
How did you come up with plans within plans
that will crash your own wedding?
You're about to engage in a battle,
but you have no idea who your enemy is.
You don't seem happy.
You also didn't
before you went to Switzerland.
If it bothers you,
please walk away from it.
Is it all because of that
that our families must be
under this obligation?
You lost your childhood memories
because of me.
Everyone uses you as a bargaining chip
to get what they want.
Whatever you want to do, do it.
If this marriage is a play,
then let's give it our all in every scene.
Starting today, I'll bring you happiness
and be your source of joy.
[Yi Phayak Chatdecha Chen]
[By Kornthas Rujeerattanavorapan]
[Kon Diao Tacha Wongteerawit]
[By Nat Natasit Uareksit]
[Kuea Keerati]
[Lian Kilen Wang]
[By Chawarin Perdpiriyawong
By Pruk Panich]
[Silsamue by Pharinyakorn Khansawa
Nuea by Koraphat Lamnoi]
[Secretary Aon by Supha Sangaworawong]
[Makorn by Penpetch Benyakul]
[Sattha by Teerapong Leowrakwong]
[Sathaporn by Tawatson Plengsiriwat]
[Stepmother Orn by Thanyaporn Sontikan]
Hello. Well...
There's something I want your help with.
- Calm down. No need to rush.
- Mr. Tacha.
Mr. Tacha.
Mr. Tacha, sir.
Please come in.
Okay.
Thank you.
Calm down.
No need to rush.
Don't rush.
Hia...
Hey, where are you going?
It's so pretty.
Do you want to touch it?
I do, but...
Come on!
I can touch it now!
- I'm touching it.
- Good job! Give me a high five.
Yep!
- I'm touching it.
- Good job! Give me a high five.
Isn't Yi much cuter
when he was little than he is now?
Hello, Dad.
Let's go.
What can I do to help you today?
I've made a decisive decision.
I'll crash the wedding, Dad.
Crash? Why?
Please listen to me first. I can explain.
I want to try again.
I don't want to be just someone
who you and Hia have to protect.
I want to be by Hia's side.
Being by Yi's side is not easy, Diao.
I told you I would take care of him,
and I mean it.
I don't want you and Hia
to keep me out of every problem.
He deserves my protection, too.
I believe I can do it
if you give me the opportunity, Dad.
Why should I give you the opportunity
to crash my son's wedding?
If I'm able to crash the wedding,
I'll be the one who breaches the contract.
The Wongteerawits will no longer
be able to use me as a bargaining chip
to take advantage of you and Hia.
The easiest way to crash the wedding is...
for me to run away.
Does Yi know about this?
He agreed.
The Chen family has paid too much
for the Wongteerawits, Dad.
It's not that we didn't get anything, Diao.
We paid the money to make up
for what happened to you.
The rest is business,
including racing track land
and having them as a partner
in an auto spare parts business.
As far as I'm concerned, it's not a loss.
But I don't like it
when my dad or the Wongteerawits
take advantage of you and Hia.
That's not the only problem.
They're your family, after all.
Therefore, I don't want there to be
a conflict in the future.
What do you advise me to do?
If you want my advice,
I'll say you don't have to be
cut off from your family.
Just make them do what they should.
You know it, right?
I and Sattha, your dad,
signed the first contract
when you were 7 years old.
We just signed another one
when you and Yi got engaged.
According to the contract,
if you two do not marry,
divorce within 5 years,
or have an affair,
and with the Chen family
being the ones breaking the contract,
we'll have to pay the Wongteerawits money
for the racing track.
But if the Wongteerawit family is at fault,
the land will belong to the Chen family.
However, if you insist
on crashing the wedding,
I have conditions for you.
Your plan will succeed
only if you can get away from my people.
I will not let you
run away that easily either.
Otherwise,
I'll be ashamed to meet my ancestors.
I'll give you 30 minutes.
Just 30 minutes?
30 minutes is enough
to make the Wongteerawits at fault
and compensate us
because you run away
and discredit us.
If you can do it,
you may do whatever you want about this.
But if you can't,
you have to let me and Yi handle it.
Okay, Dad.
Great.
You've got this, Tacha Chen.
I'm still one of the Wongteerawits, though.
Then, please excuse me.
Goodbye, Dad.
Wait, Diao.
I just want to tell you
that you still have your family here.
I welcomed you into the Chen family.
No matter how you handle the Wongteerawits,
you'll always be my son.
Okay, Dad.
Goodbye.
Whatever Nong Diao decides,
I'll be on his side.
Do you actually want to get married?
Don't just mess around.
I can't make it obvious.
In order for his plan to succeed,
I must pretend I know nothing about it.
Then, send your people after him.
After that, I'll tell him
that you forced me to get him back.
Damn you, Yi.
If you make mistakes this time,
I will sell all of the Chen family's assets
since we won't have any honor
or dignity left.
Don't make any mistakes.
Yes, Dad.
Great.
The job of the clan's chief
is to protect it, not to destroy it.
I'm not doing this only for him, Dad.
You know it.
It's a good thing
that you do it for someone you love.
Consider the advantages
as profit.
Yi.
Chen family members must be strong.
However,
strong people do cry.
If you want to cry, do so.
I'll be right here.
Dad...
You're amazing, Yi.
Thanks, Dad.
Yi...
Yes, Dad?
Is it tiring to be my son?
It's not as tiring as having me as a son.
Why don't the numbers match?
Why don't the figures
in the revenue summary by Sathaporn
match up with this one?
What happened to the money?
Get everyone in the accounting department
to my room now.
Bring the accounting documents
here as well.
Did you take care of everything?
Yes, sir.
Does Yi know about this yet?
He does, sir.
However, he doesn't know the details.
He will come to see you shortly, sir.
If they want to play those dirty tricks,
they'd better not blame us for being cruel.
Someone has been stalking me
for a while now.
It took a while
until they lost track of me.
You should hire
more security guards here, Dad.
I might not be the only one
they're stalking.
Who do they work for?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You're doing this again.
It's not that I didn't want
to use your people.
I didn't tell you
because they were just stalking me.
I wasn't sure.
I've sent someone, though.
Can I still ask for your help, Aon?
Do you still have time to work for me
if you also work for my dad?
Yi.
But you're still my first priority, sir.
I've been working for Mr. Makorn
since you got into an accident
because he's worried about you, sir.
You don't need to worry, sir.
I can still help you with anything.
Does that mean everything that I know...
I told you
you could use my stuff and people.
Is there anything else I don't know
besides the fact that
my secretary works for you?
Easy.
Listen to Aon's report first.
According to our engineer's report
on the car,
we discovered that...
Hello, Mr. Aon. I'm Nuea.
Someone used a piece of cloth
to plug the brake booster vacuum hose,
so the brake wasn't working.
After examining that piece of cloth
and the CCTV footage at your house,
the person who tampered
with Mr. Tacha's car was...
Mr. Tem of the Wongteerawits, sir.
How did he get into the house?
One of Mr. Makorn's guards...
also worked for them, sir.
That guard must have known
your guards' work schedule, sir.
Where the hell is he now?
We caught him
as he was trying to escape, sir.
He's now been brought back to the mansion.
He confessed
and blamed Mr. Tem
for giving him the money.
Easy.
Teach him a lesson
as per the Chen family's rules.
Yes, sir.
Only Tem?
Someone used Mr. Tem
to cause the accident, sir.
The actual wire-puller is...
Mr. Sathaporn Wongteerawit, sir.
He's Nong Diao's uncle.
Yes, sir.
I had no intention of killing Kon Diao.
How was I supposed to know
that Hia Yi would drive that car?
Did you do this alone, Mr. Tem?
Let me go!
My dad would never let you do this to me.
Even after he found out
you were going to injure Mr. Tacha?
Mr. Sattha...
doesn't know it yet, does he?
I didn't mean to do it.
Uncle Sathaporn made me do it.
Mr. Tem got used
because he thought Mr. Sattha...
would give Mr. Tacha
half of the Wongteerawit's land.
He, as a younger brother,
was worried he wouldn't get anything
because Mr. Sathaporn told him so.
And in fact, both Mr. Tem and Miss Tam...
are Mr. Sattha's biological children, sir.
They are not just his stepchildren,
as we first assumed.
As for Mrs. Orn, their mother,
in addition to having had
an affair with Mr. Sattha
since he was still married
to Mr. Tacha's mother,
she's now having an affair
with Mr. Sathaporn,
Mr. Sattha's younger brother
and the wire-puller for all of this.
Why did you get us here? Ouch!
- Let go of my daughter!
- It would be impossible
to claim that Mrs. Orn
was not involved in this.
Tem, why are you here?
Aon, why did you get my son here?
I have some questions for you,
Mrs. Orn, Miss Tam, and Mr. Tem,
regarding Mr. Sathaporn.
Then go ask him!
Why would you get us here?
Let go of me!
Where is that damn Sathaporn?
No more stalking the Chens.
Their weakness is the Wongteerawits.
Hunt Kon Diao down.
We'll see if you can catch me this time,
you damn Chens!
[Mr. Phayak Chatdecha Chen]
We still haven't found him.
Mr. Sathaporn was able to run away
from our people, sir.
Hire more guards.
Take good care of everyone.
Yes, sir.
Why are you here?
- Isn't Diao here with you?
- I'll just get straight to the point.
I don't know how you guys work.
A huge amount of money has vanished,
but you're still sitting around
doing nothing.
I just noticed it as well.
Someone's looking into it.
Right.
I don't want to be involved
in the private matters
of the Wongteerawits any longer
if it's not about my family.
I hope you can handle it.
However,
I wasn't here to only talk about this.
Sathaporn, your brother,
was behind my accident.
Not only Sathaporn,
but Orn, your current wife,
and Tem, your son,
were also involved.
What are you talking about?
See all the evidence for yourself.
It doesn't matter if you believe it or not.
The car that overturned was given
to Nong Diao by my dad
as an engagement gift.
Do you remember that?
Tem also does.
The person who tampered with the car
was Tem.
This is impossible.
Tem wouldn't do that.
They're siblings.
Are you sure
that siblings wouldn't hurt each other?
I'd like you to do me a favor.
Don't tell Kon Diao anything yet.
I'll handle all of this.
I will not let Kon Diao hurt again,
no matter why or who,
even if that person
is his biological father.
Let go of me! Let me go!!
Let me go!
- Let me go! Let go of me!!
- Catch him!
Stay still!
A group of people
was following Mr. Tacha, sir.
What?
However,
he's now safe with your guards, sir.
And we've captured them, sir.
Where?
[Nong Diao]
Hello, Nong Diao.
Where are you? Are you alright?
I'm alright, Hia.
Do you know who they are?
I'm not sure.
However, I'm fine.
Mr. Chenne helped me
before it was too late.
Mr. Chenne?
Let go of me! Let me go!!
- Let me go! Let go of me!!
- Catch him!
Let me go!
Stay still!
Stop it!
Mr. Chenne.
Hey!
Hey! Run!
Hey! Run! Come on!
Your dad's guards and your guards
are now chasing them down.
Where are you? I'll be right there.
Yi, just calm down and talk to him first.
Calm down, Hia.
Don't worry about me.
I'm totally fine now.
Okay. Don't be scared.
My guards just informed me
that they'd captured them.
Okay, Hia. Thank you.
Nong Diao,
can I pick you up?
I'm not at ease.
It's alright, Hia.
You don't have to worry about me.
I'll get something done first.
See you at home.
Okay.
I'll be right back when I get this done.
Is Kon Diao alright?
He's safe now.
Yes?
We've found out where Sathaporn is going.
Get the car.
You don't have to. I'll handle this.
I raised you to be a businessman,
not a thug.
Just keep your hands off of this.
I can't.
You can't handle it your way.
You just told me
you didn't raise me to be a thug.
I will handle this.
I will never let anyone, no matter who,
ruin our family again.
Aon.
Don't spoil him too much.
If he's intractable, you can come back
and work for me at the mansion.
I still want to help
and work for Mr. Phayak, sir.
You too, Aon.
Just forget what happened
and don't think of it as indebtedness.
Although Yi helped you
when your father passed away,
don't forget that he passed away
because of him.
I like working for him, sir.
Well, thank you.
Please take care of him.
Yes, sir.
Thank you for saving me, Mr. Chenne.
It's alright. You don't have to thank me.
Thank you, thank you, and thank you.
Dada, I'm hungry.
This baby boy...
Actually, you don't have to take me home.
I can go home on my own.
I'm used to it.
I've received your wedding invitation card.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Mr. Chenne.
I may not be available that day,
so I may not go.
It's alright.
Then, please excuse me.
Bye-bye, Chun.
Are you leaving now?
Alone?
Aren't you lonely?
- Chun...
- Yes?
Are you lonely?
I've never been lonely
because I have Dada with me.
I'll get going now.
Bye-bye, Chun.
Coach Diao.
Yes, Mr. Chenne?
Are you sure you don't want a lift home?
It's fine, Mr. Chenne. Thank you.
Bye-bye, Chun.
Come on, dear. Get in the car.
[Wongteerawit]
I wanted the best for you.
You having a decent place to live
and attending a good school...
is enough.
I don't have a lot of expectations.
I love you, Diao.
Dad.
Why are you here?
Are you here alone?
Did something happen?
I'm fine.
What happened?
Has something happened to our family?
No.
Are you here alone?
Leave, now.
Dad, wait!
I told you to leave!
Isn't your wedding starting early tomorrow?
I'm sorry, Dad,
for not telling you this myself.
Don't say anything...
I don't have anything else to give you.
Why would you say that?
I don't want anything.
I've never wanted it.
You've never asked me what I wanted
or what I wanted to do.
You just assumed
what you did was best for me.
Everything I did was for you.
Only you!
Does that include
getting me a new mom
and new siblings
and sending me to the UK?
All I wanted when I was younger was...
you, Dad.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry for what?
If you are sorry,
you should be able to tell me
what you're sorry for.
All I want to know is,
have you ever loved me?
I got it, Dad.
No matter if you love me or not,
the Wongteerawits are no longer my home.
I will never let you use me again.
You're my home, Hia.
You're my home, too.
I love you, Hia.
I love you, too.
Welcome home, Nong Diao.
Will you actually run away
from our wedding?
I've made up my mind,
and I'm not going to change it.
A mission to betray my Chihuahua
has now begun!
You think you're going to win?
I'm not going to pull my punches.
You'd better keep your guard up then,
Tacha Chen.
Hia Yi's guards are now
at every exit.
You have to be very careful.
Kon Diao just walked past me.
Why didn't you stop him?
If I did, it wouldn't be fun.
Jeez, this a**hole!
I will not let you run away from me
ever again.
Please stay with me
and let me love you.
I will never let you down.
I will always love you, Kon Diao,
and my love for you will last forever.