Warning: All occurrences happened
in this series are fictional
and for an entertainment purpose only.
Viewer discretion required.
The Chen family has paid too much
for the Wongteerawits, Dad.
Hia deserves my protection, too.
The easiest way to crash the wedding is...
for me to run away.
Your plan will succeed
only if you can get away from my people.
In order for his plan to succeed,
I must pretend I know nothing about it.
Don't make any mistakes.
Someone has been stalking me
for a while now.
It took a while
until they lost track of me.
You should hire
more security guards here, Dad.
I might not be the only one
they're stalking.
Tem wouldn't do that.
They're siblings.
No matter why or who,
even if that person is
Nong Diao's biological father,
I will not let Nong Diao hurt again.
[Yi Phayak Chatdecha Chen]
[By Kornthas Rujeerattanavorapan]
[Kon Diao Tacha Wongteerawit]
[By Nat Natasit Uareksit]
[Kuea Keerati]
[Lian Kilen Wang]
[By Chawarin Perdpiriyawong
By Pruk Panich]
[Silsamue by Pharinyakorn Khansawa
Nuea by Koraphat Lamnoi]
[Secretary Aon by Supha Sangaworawong]
[Makorn by Penpetch Benyakul]
[Sattha by Teerapong Leowrakwong]
[Sathaporn by Tawatson Plengsiriwat]
[Stepmother Orn by Thanyaporn Sontikan]
Nong Diao.
Yes, Hia?
Are you ready for today's event?
Then...
I want you to meet someone first.
Who is it, Hia?
- Oh! Hia...
- Hia.
Nong Diao, this is Ing-ing Chatchada,
and this is Aun-aun Chatchanok.
They're my sisters.
And the most gorgeous lady
sitting here, smiling, is...
- Your mom?
- Right.
Hello, Mom.
Come take a seat, dear.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Welcome to our family, dear.
I didn't go out to greet you
because my feet hurt.
Also, Yi didn't tell me
he would take you to meet me now.
It's totally fine, Mom.
I'm the one who should be apologizing
- for misunderstanding you.
- What misunderstanding?
- Well...
- Well, Nong Diao...
thought that these girls
were my mistresses.
I didn't know you had sisters.
And... you two are absolutely stunning.
It's fine. We're not mad at you.
Actually, I'm older than you.
And Aun-aun is one year younger, right?
Right.
We were so worried
that we were the source of your argument.
But now, seeing you two getting married...
makes me blissful.
You two are the perfect match.
Diao, all 4 Chats are here today.
Chatchai, Chatdecha,
Chatchada, and Chatchanok.
You may rest assured now.
I can assure you that
he's not having an affair with anyone.
He's madly in love with you.
He also told me a lot of things about you.
So, from now on,
we're not strangers.
Okay.
Please bear with my son, dear.
He's stubborn, in denial,
grumpy, and cranky.
Mom,
that's enough.
That's not because of you.
- Neither of us is like that.
- Right.
It's probably inherited from his father.
Hia, from now on,
bring Kon Diao to meet us often.
I want a lovely brother.
I'm getting tired of a cruel brother.
I'm also happy...
to have an older sister
- and a younger sister...
- No!
Don't look at them.
Don't be lured by these girls.
You can only look at me.
Jeez, he's so possessive.
You've been like this since you were young,
and it hasn't changed at all.
Kon Diao is not one of your dolls, Hia.
Exactly.
I don't play with dolls.
That's enough of you.
When you guys meet, you always fight.
Anyway, bring him to see me often.
We're family now.
Nong Diao,
although your name means "alone,"
you are no longer alone.
- Can I have a hug?
- Yes.
- Come on.
- Let's hug.
Show some love.
What was it like meeting my mom?
She's gorgeous.
She's also very kind.
While she was hugging me,
I almost cried.
Why would you cry?
I missed my mom.
I'm not sure how it would be
if she were still alive.
She would love you
and be so proud of you.
Why would she be proud?
I'm not good at anything.
Who told you that?
You're a good person.
You excel in studies
and a tough sport like Taekwondo.
You're a good friend.
You're both a dad and a mom
to that bulging-eyed dog.
How come you're not good at anything?
I'm very proud that I'll get to marry you.
What are you doing?
Why did you close the elevator?
Will you actually run away
from our wedding?
We've talked about this, Hia.
Are you sure you're doing this?
Don't you trust me?
It's not like that.
I just want you to reconsider it.
I've made up my mind,
and I'm not going to change it.
Then, can you tell me
what you're planning to do?
My plan is to...
keep you in the dark.
Nong Diao! You have gone too far!
I won't pull my punches then!
3+15
+14+7
+18+1
+20+19
Swap the numbers
P.S. Swap them
and then enter the actual result!
Why would you have to
make it so complicated, Kuea?
Can you tell us...
how you two met?
I can't. Too lazy.
It's a long story.
Uh...
What's your first impression of Mr. Tacha?
Pretty cute. I wanted to tease him.
And when did you realize
you were falling in love with him?
No idea. Can't recall.
If I take it off and place it here,
it'll for sure be stolen.
I'll find a way to get it back later.
Aon!
Please end the interview right now.
Why?
Mr. Phayak has an urgent task.
But we just started the interview.
- If it's not finished...
- We'll inform you when we're ready.
Please.
Are you all set?
A mission to betray my Chihuahua
has now begun!
Diao,
Hia Yi's guards are now at every exit.
You have to be very careful.
Get to the front of the hotel.
Find Nuea and Sil.
They'll get you a cab,
and he'll take you to my secret house.
What about Makorn's guards?
You don't have to worry about that.
Those engineering grads
and their acting skills won't fail you.
Stick to the plan, Sil.
What happened?
- Over there!
- Where?
There!
There's someone suspicious over there!
Right!
Wait, no!
There is!
There isn't!
- What do you mean exactly?
- There's really someone there!
It's terrifying!
See? My friend is too scared to speak!
- No.
- He is!
Don't be scared.
It's fine if he's still there.
- Go get him!
- There's someone suspicious.
Let's take a look.
Hurry!
I undertake the precept...
- to refrain from incorrect speech.
- To refrain from incorrect speech.
- Amen.
- Amen...
What if I get caught?
Congratulations, then.
I don't want that.
Sorry.
I got carried away enjoying the performance
of those engineering grads in the lobby.
Did you just say "got carried away"?
Was Hia Yi in the lobby?
Um... I didn't see him.
Don't waste our time.
In, come with me.
Change your outfit.
- Do I have to?
- Yes!
Just change it and do nothing.
Be on standby.
As for you, Diao,
give me the keycard.
Oh, right. Here.
If you want anything, just tell us.
In and I will be on standby.
I wish you good luck.
Come on!
1, 2, 3!
Yeah!!
Kuea, can we swap roles?
You should play as Kon Diao.
You went to acting classes, didn't you?
That's impossible.
They'll recognize me once they see my face.
Keep in mind that
I am Kirin!
♫Hey, you cutie!♫
Jeez, what a superstar!
We're the production team,
and we've come to photograph
and interview Mr. Tacha.
Why are you here, Mr. Kirin?
I'm one of Kon Diao's groomsmen.
That's awesome!
In that case,
after we finish interviewing Mr. Tacha,
may we please interview you?
Sure.
You can me interview first.
Kon Diao's not feeling very well.
Alright.
So... Shall we start?
It was just a group of ill-wishers
attempting to incite a disturbance.
However, the higher-ups demanded that
we not make any mistakes this time.
- Yes, sir.
- Go.
Kon Diao just walked past me.
Why didn't you stop him?
If I did, it wouldn't be fun.
It would be too easy.
I want to see more of your efforts, Yi.
Jeez, this asshole!
Where are you now?
At a restaurant.
What will you do, Yi?
There's only 12 minutes left.
I'll get even with you later.
Although it's highly competitive in Korea,
it's a lot of fun.
And... what about...
Oh, Kon Diao...
You fell asleep.
He must be exhausted.
He didn't get much sleep last night.
I don't think he can give an interview.
I'll inform you right away once he's ready.
Well, okay.
Thank you so much, Mr. Kirin.
Then, please excuse us.
Yes.
Thank you.
Hey! How did you get in here?
You don't have a keycard, do you?
Hey! You can't be in here!
It's a private room!
- Mr. Tacha.
- Stop!
Mr. Tacha's not in the room, sir.
Come on.
What should we do?
I think it's time to implement Plan C.
Hello, Kuea. What's next?
Kuea, hello?
Why is it broken now?
Kon Diao!
- Kon Diao!
- Winner?
- Plan C.
- Plan C?
Not B?
It must be C now.
We've found Sathaporn, sir.
Where?
He was fleeing the country
through natural routes.
Our people are taking him back here, sir.
Handle him
the way Yi wants.
Yes, sir.
Where's Kon Diao?
We haven't found him, sir.
I'll give you 10 minutes.
If Kon Diao doesn't show up,
I'll cancel the wedding.
Okay.
You understand what that means, right?
If the wedding is canceled
and the Wongteerawit family is at fault,
I will be held accountable
per the contract.
The Wongteerawit family's ownership
of the racing track land
will belong to the Chen family.
But sir...
A deal is a deal.
If you took the land,
we wouldn't have anything left.
Come on, Mr. Sattha.
Can't you figure it out yet?
Everything that went down
was due to your selfishness.
You've been using Kon Diao
as a bargaining chip
to take advantage of us for too long.
I love Kon Diao.
I've never thought to do that to my son.
Suit yourself.
Find him, then.
As for Tem,
I'll have to report him to the police.
Please, sir.
Please forgive my son.
He's just a child.
He knows nothing.
Do you now realize the anguish of a father
who has been blackmailed?
Hi, there.
Hello. Hi.
Whoa! Hi.
- Enough, babe.
- What?
That's enough.
- We have to greet everyone, babe.
- That's enough.
Well, their wedding is
actually smaller than ours.
The wedding's small, but the problem's big.
What do you mean?
Kon Diao ran away.
What?!
She's laughing.
So funny.
- Smile. Come on, smile.
- Love it.
Uh... I'm in the lobby.
Right. You can turn there.
Thank you.
Winner.
Go to the lobby now.
Sil and Nuea are waiting.
Congratulations! You can do it!
Come on, hurry up.
Just go. Bye-bye!
Go! Bye-bye.
Mr. Tacha!
Wait, sir!
By and large,
it's all your fault, Mr. Sattha.
I apologize, sir.
What I've done is wrong.
I'm a crook.
Please accept my apologies
and penalize me.
Please don't do anything to Tem.
When will you stop cleaning up
after your son?
You've been raising your children
wrong all along.
You've spoiled them too much.
I'm talking about your daughter as well.
As for Tem and Sathaporn,
I'll have to report the case to the police
and let it be prosecuted
according to the law.
And please let this be the last time.
After this,
the Chen family and the Wongteerawits
will no longer be under any obligation.
Do you understand, Mr. Sattha?
Sir...
our people have found Mr. Tacha.
It seems like
Kon Diao just saved you again.
Still, I want to hear from Kon Diao
if he still wants to marry Yi.
If he doesn't want to, let him.
You have no right to make him do anything.
Understood?
Sir, please wait. My friend's coming.
- Okay. Sure.
- Okay.
[Kuea: Plan's changed!!!]
Uh, excuse me.
Do you want to make merit with me?
- Is that for a donation?
- Yes.
Sil! Wrong timing.
But it's over now.
Kuea just texted me
that the plan's changed.
What's our plan now?
I'm absolutely lost.
It's Plan... W.
Sorry to keep you waiting, sir.
Here's for your wait.
Here's my donation.
Sil.
It's his.
It'll create positive karma for
Hia Yi and Kon Diao.
Sil, this is a wedding.
Their love will last a long time.
Fine. Come on. Let's go.
What's next, Kuea?
Hello? Hello!
2 minutes left.
Gotcha!
Hia!
Come on now. Stop playing.
Let's go inside.
No, I won't.
I'm about to be free.
If you're worried about your family,
just go inside and see for yourself.
Come with me.
No. If you want me to go with you,
you have to win me first.
Are you being stubborn?
I'm not.
You are.
You think you're going to win?
I'm not going to pull my punches,
Mr. Phayak Chen.
You'd better keep your guard up then,
Tacha Chen.
I haven't yet agreed to change my surname.
Dad!
- Ouch!
- Gotcha!
Fine! You want me to go all out, don't you?
Stop!
I'll handle it.
Nong, how did you get here?
Who took you here?
How did you end up here?
Nong Diao.
I told you.
No matter how many times you run away,
I will always bring you back.
Your time to be stubborn is over, honey.
I will not let you run away from me
ever again.
Please stay with me
and let me love you.
I will never let you down.
What if I'm stubborn?
I will still love you.
What if I'm naughty?
It won't change.
No matter if you're one of
the Wongteerawits or the Chens,
I will always love you, Kon Diao,
and my love for you will last forever.
Will you marry me?
Kiss him! Kiss him!
Kiss him! Kiss him!!
Kiss him!! Kiss him!!!
Kiss him!!! Kiss him!!!!
Congrats, Diao.
Thank you so much, Kuea.
Thank you for giving me life,
a life in which I met Hia
and became a part of his life.
I'm grateful for everything
you've done for me.
However, from now on,
I will no longer be one
of the Wongteerawits.
Even so, you'll always have my respect.
Regarding the remaining land
of the racing track
owned by the Wongteerawit family,
I will ask Makorn to buy it
at a reasonable price.
This will be the last thing
I can do for you.
Please stop any further attempts.
From now on,
I hope you'll be happy, Dad.
Kon Diao,
I'm sorry.
I sincerely apologize.
I...
I don't deserve a wonderful son like you.
I love you, Kon Diao.
I love you too, Dad.
Kiss!
Kiss!!
Kiss him! Kiss!
Kiss him! Kiss him!!
Kiss him!! Kiss him!!
Do it, sir!
Kiss him!
Where's my reward?
What reward?
You didn't win, Hia.
Kon Diao won because the time ran out.
Is that so?
The time ran out...
after Yi hugged Kon Diao.
It's a draw, then.
Love wins.
Love always wins.
I'm tired.
Of course, you are.
You spent that much energy running away.
Are you tired?
No.
I can play tag with you hundreds more times
if, in the end, you'll marry me.
Thank you so much for today,
bulging-eyed doggo.
You did a great job.
I shall appoint you
as the Chen family's spy from now on.
Your full name will be...
Natasha Romanong Woof-woof Chen.
What?
Was she your accomplice?
When did you talk about this?
Cheater!
Just know that
I've reconciled with Nong now.
I mean, Natasha Romanong.
From now on, don't make fun of me
by saying that I'd eat her, okay?
Fine.
The only Nong I'll eat out...
is you, Nong Diao.
Hold on, Hia.
Nong, you have to leave now.
I'm sorry, Nong,
but this scene is not for children.
Are you ready?
Eat up,
Diao, my beloved son.
- Okay, Dad.
- Mm.
How come he's your beloved son?
What about me?
You've already fallen off the radar.
Have you figured it out yet?
Just admit it, Dad.
I'm just a gardener's son, right?
You just adopted me, didn't you?
That's nonsense.
If you were not my son,
I wouldn't let Kon Diao marry you.
Fine, then.
- Right, Diao...
- Yes?
Why don't you bring Nong here as well?
I've prepared a room for her.
It's very cute and lovely.
I'll show you the room.
Really, Dad?
I don't want to bother you, though.
Wait, what did I miss?
Am I being kept out of the loop?
Did you make a room
for that bulging-eyed dog?
You guys have gone too far.
That bulging-eyed dog's
forgotten her roots, hasn't she?
What a cocky dog!
- Why would you swear at her?
- What?
What a foul-mouthed person you are!
- Diao.
- Yes?
Do you want a new husband?
I'll get you one.
Really, Dad?
I'm thinking of finding one, too.
You can't, Dad!
You're so good at taking jokes, huh?
You're married, Mr. Tacha.
You're not single anymore.
What about a celebrity, Diao?
- I know a lot of them.
- That sounds great, Dad.
[2029]
We've been married for three years,
yet it feels like yesterday.
I'm shy to admit it.
It may sound like I'm bragging,
but it's true that...
marrying Hia is the best decision
I've ever made.
Every day is a great day because of him.
Papa's here!
I'm home, dear.
You have balloons!
I was born with the name "Kon Diao,"
meaning "alone."
Here's your birthday gift.
I hoped to be a loving family
for someone one day,
but today, it exceeded my hopes.
Kon Diao, let's go.
Yes, Hia.
Not only Hia,
Wait up.
...but we do have Le Ling
as our lovely daughter now.
Come on. Let's go.
Ling-ling had been alone before.
But today,
she has both of us as her fathers.
♫Happy birthday to you♫
♫Happy birthday to you, Happy♫
And recently,
we just received
the most wonderful present,
Le Xi, our happiness and hope.
The Chen family line will be carried on.
There!
Don't look!
- I already did.
- No more looking, okay?
Don't look, okay?
Why can't we have a large family
when there's so much love
and happiness to go around?
I'm glad that
we can share love in our family.
We'll embrace this love
and care for one another as a family.
Hia,
we now have the rest of our lives
to spend together.
You will get to hold us,
and we will hold you forever and ever.
Your love inspires me
to be a better person.
Me too.
Papa, Daddy, ready?
- We are, honey.
- Come on, Ling-ling.
I hope that this can happen equally
everywhere in the world,
that we can feel happy
that we have been granted this right,
and that I, Kon Diao,
will never be alone again.
This is my home.